<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-04-26T16:12:02+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ifuryst</title><subtitle>📝 &amp; 💭 </subtitle><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 69/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-69-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 69/100days"/><published>2025-04-26T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-26T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-69-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-69-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣9️⃣</p> <p>I suddenly remembered one of the reasons why I started this 100 Days Build in Public challenge: Simon Willison.</p> <p>He’s an incredibly prolific writer. One time he talked about how he manages to be so productive, and he mentioned that he once did 100 consecutive days of content creation. Combined with his years of writing experience, he can now quickly turn the information he absorbs into writing every day, maintaining a high-output state. This idea stuck with me, and that night, on a bit of an impulse, I decided to give it a try myself.</p> <p>The “power of 100” is real — once you go through it, you truly experience all the ups and downs. I think it’s worth doing at least once. It’s like a burst of impulsive passion or impulse spending — only through time and real experience can you grasp the real sweetness and bitterness of it.</p> <p>Although I’ve always believed that frontend or client-side work is more visible — easier to show results — while backend work (especially in the early stages) often looks like simple CRUD operations until it reaches a certain scale, I’ve realized that doing frontend or client development is actually incredibly demanding and often underappreciated. If you really want to pursue a perfect experience and polish the presentation, it requires a massive amount of time and energy. From my past experience, frontend and client-side work usually consumes a disproportionate amount of effort — maybe because I’m not a seasoned frontend or mobile engineer.</p> <p>Now, with tools like Cursor + ChatGPT, many things are easier to cover, but the real challenge lies in continuous tuning and testing. Many times, you think you’ve communicated your idea clearly, but the actual result can turn out quite different.</p> <p>Today, I finished polishing some basic add/delete functionalities. Even for a seemingly simple page, the information density is very high, and what it requires is built up layer by layer.</p> <p>Here’s a summary of my current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend Development (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client-side Development (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel you fit the following, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Can stay consistent</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Have passion and interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣9️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 68/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-68-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 68/100days"/><published>2025-04-25T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-25T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-68-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-68-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day6️⃣8️⃣</p> <p>As expected, having influential people with strong traffic help promote the project had a great impact, leading to a rapid boost. However, the key lies in choosing the right direction and track — only then can others immediately recognize the quality of your project. Choosing the right track and then working hard is crucial.</p> <p>Speaking of which, Iter-X’s problem lies in its business model. Actually, I kind of want to ask Junyu Wang what he thinks about this [DOGE]. His project, “Reading Room,” shows a similar shadow to what I’m experiencing. I don’t know how he thought through his product; I’ve only seen glimpses of his journey through his articles. Somehow, I feel a one-sided resonance with him — seeing a bit of myself in his experiences. Of course, it’s just a thought; I don’t really have a way to reach out to him.</p> <p>I feel that from these couple of days until after May 1st, my project progress might slow down significantly. In a way, the next month looks pretty unpredictable. I’ve been considering whether I should shift to building a long-term cycle product. After nearly 100 days of high-intensity push — almost a 007 (work-life blend) commitment to this side project — I’m thinking about finding a better balance, especially since I’m not “all-in” on a single project.</p> <p>Recently, I’ve also had some new ideas about the product positioning. Perhaps this project can evolve toward the form of products like Devin or Manus, but with a strong focus on the travel field. It would allow for a gradual, progressive functional layering. Though this idea is not fully matured yet.</p> <p>I’ll keep absorbing a large amount of information, working on entropy reduction, and see what might eventually come out of it. 🙂</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend Development (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client Development (Flutter): 57%</li> <li>Data Preparation: 14%</li> </ol> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you think you fit the following profile, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Able to stay persistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day6️⃣8️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 67/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-67-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 67/100days"/><published>2025-04-24T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-24T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-67-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-67-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣7️⃣</p> <p>Marketing is crucial, especially in the early stage of a project. My two recent open-source projects both gained initial momentum by being shared in the right circles and platforms. They got in front of the right audience from day one. Then it’s all about expanding exposure—getting your product or project seen in more places. Even if it doesn’t attract attention immediately, it can have a long-term effect. People will gradually trickle in. What you need to do is keep iterating.</p> <p>Even though these are just open-source projects, the approach is essentially a PMF (Product-Market Fit) journey. I’m learning a lot through this:</p> <p>1️⃣ Good wine still needs marketing. A great idea may go unnoticed if you don’t know how to market it—and you might miss the window of opportunity.</p> <p>2️⃣ Sometimes you’re not sure if your idea is actually a good one. But if someone gives you that initial validation, it can make a huge difference. And even if the first idea isn’t the one, it might evolve into something powerful. Often, you don’t realize its potential until later.</p> <p>3️⃣ Speed is everything, especially in the age of AI. I keep telling my friends this: if you have an idea, just do it. Even a one-week delay might cost you the moment. The goal isn’t to build something perfect—it’s to go from 0 to 1. You’ll likely get something valuable out of it.</p> <p>4️⃣ Build your own distribution channels. Think of yourself as the maker—but also the distributor. Channels matter.</p> <p>That’s about it. Easier said than done, but action speaks louder than words. By the way, someone influential tagged my project today. 🤞 Hope it brings more visibility by this Friday.</p> <p>Honestly, I’ve been treating this #100Days challenge like writing a diary, haha. The truth is, I can’t always produce solid progress every single day. Sometimes my commits aren’t full features or polished modules. People are visual creatures—I get that. I’m not breaking things down into technical pieces on purpose. Also, I’m not a content creator, so I don’t have the skills to “cook up” flashy updates. I just share my thoughts and recent learnings—freely and casually.</p> <p>Current progress: • Prototype design &amp; UI/UX: 33% • Backend (Go): 60% • Client (Flutter): 57% • Data: 14%</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you match any of the following, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>You’re consistent</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣7️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 66/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-66-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 66/100days"/><published>2025-04-23T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-23T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-66-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-66-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣6️⃣</p> <p>Not much progress today. I’ve been heavily focused on MCP lately, and also experimenting with travel planning done directly via unwrapped LLMs. It gave me some new ideas for the product. I’m starting to believe that the moat for this type of travel planning product might lie in data:</p> <p>1️⃣ First, having a reliable and objective factual dataset can significantly suppress hallucinations and maximize the user experience. This is also a key reason why RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) is so popular. I think many LLM-based vertical products can actually be classified as RAG applications.</p> <p>2️⃣ Second, user data. With ChatGPT’s new Memory feature, I think we’re witnessing a real game-changer. Making users feel “wow, this thing gets me” relies entirely on user data + data generated during usage.</p> <p>For products in this specific category, different monetization models will highlight different strengths — for example, some might compete based on their supply chain. Just some food for thought.</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 56%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel like you fit the following description, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>You can stay committed</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣6️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 65/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-65-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 65/100days"/><published>2025-04-22T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-22T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-65-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-65-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣5️⃣</p> <p>Amap’s support for Flutter is honestly pretty disappointing — the latest version (3.0.0) is still from three years ago. Feels kinda rough. For now, I’ll make do with it and figure out a better solution later. The basic map rendering is more or less done. Currently, I’m using a simple “Day.N” format to represent point-to-point routes. In the future, I’ll replace those with POI stickers. Up next is adding functionality to insert and remove stops in the itinerary. After that, I’ll move on to the expense tracking module.</p> <p>Time really flies. Things have been pretty hectic lately, and progress has slowed down a bit. On top of that, a lot of teammates have been walking away one by one. It’s a familiar scene — in the end, it’s rare to find people who truly walk the whole path with you. And that’s okay. I’ll tweak things and keep pushing forward.</p> <p>Also, I recently open-sourced two AI-related projects, which got a lot of love from developers. I’m planning to carve out some dedicated time to grow one of them into a full-fledged SaaS service. That said, I’ll still keep iterating on Iter-X. I’m just not sure if the original milestones can still be hit on time. But since I’ve set off on this path, there’s no turning back — this is the commitment and perseverance needed to walk a road less traveled.</p> <p>Mentally, I feel pretty great every day. Physically, though, my carbon-based body is having trouble keeping up. I went for my first swim of the year this afternoon, and I plan to swim twice a week moving forward. Gotta keep my body in shape to keep the output going strong. It’s late now — good night!</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>Current Progress Overview:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 56%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you match the following traits, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Consistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Passionate</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣5️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 64/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-64-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 64/100days"/><published>2025-04-21T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-21T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-64-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-64-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣4️⃣</p> <p>Immersed in a sea of data, endlessly exploring. Today I’ve been calibrating the transformation from WGS84 to GCJ02 coordinate systems. Some of the previous data had location inaccuracies, so I’m adjusting the logic to fix it. Hopefully I can finish refining the scripts this week and start large-scale POI processing. Related images are also being crawled, and will later be uploaded in batches to OSS.</p> <p>When dealing with images and videos, the two most costly factors are usually: 1. Storage and 2. Bandwidth. Storage tends to be cheaper, and we can optimize costs by implementing cold/hot storage separation. But bandwidth is where costs can spiral, so we pay extra attention there.</p> <p>Typically, we generate several thumbnail versions of each image. In most cases, a thumbnail of just a few dozen KB is sufficient, especially on mobile screens. With lossless compression, we can reduce file sizes of high-res images significantly. And we can even sacrifice some resolution without noticeable impact to the human eye — unless you zoom in. That’s why we strike a balance between visual quality and cost by generating a few common thumbnail sizes.</p> <p>Some systems even support on-the-fly image resizing via URL parameters. This avoids the need to store multiple versions, though it requires generating images in real-time. However, if paired with a CDN, you only need to generate the image on the first request, which is totally acceptable. There’s no silver bullet — only solutions that best match your scenario and budget.</p> <p>Progress so far:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 55%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you identify with the following, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>You’re persistent</li> <li>You’ve got dreams</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣4️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 63/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-63-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 63/100days"/><published>2025-04-20T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-20T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-63-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-63-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣3️⃣</p> <p>The current map tiles don’t offer enough customization, so I’ll just make do for now. I’ve adjusted the overall color scheme first—starting with subtraction before addition. Making the map truly smooth and easy to use will definitely take some serious effort.</p> <p>Today, I came across a sentence: “Netflix today is very different. It’s not a library — it’s an experience.”</p> <p>While the original article had a different message, this line really resonated with me and sparked some thoughts. The idea is that Netflix used to be more like a library or a search engine—you’d come, find a movie, and watch it. Now, it’s become more of an experience. It uses your watch history, preferences, and recommendation algorithms to push content you’re likely to enjoy. In other words, the content is no longer the star—the experience is.</p> <p>Of course, this is open to interpretation. For instance, in travel, many people have access to the same data—but is content what really matters? To a degree, yes. Platforms like Xiaohongshu have built strong ecosystems and moats around content. But when it comes to travel, maybe what matters more is experience. While today’s technology might not yet offer true end-to-end service, we can still deliver a solid user experience. Sadly, as companies chase profit and growth, this often gets deprioritized or lost.</p> <p>Experience might actually be a key driver of user retention. It’s something worth reflecting on. Today, many indie developers are capable of creating functional products—tools that hit the “library” level of usefulness. But crafting a truly great experience is another matter entirely. That’s a crucial dividing line. With enough time and energy, many people can build a passable product—but standing out requires real skill, insight, and depth. It’s like that old saying: “Going from 0 to 60 is easy. From 60 to 100 is where it gets tough.”</p> <p>Still, it’s not impossible. The resources we have at our disposal within a given timeframe are more or less fixed. What we can grow is our awareness, our exposure to diverse people and ideas, and our ability to stay grounded. In a fast-moving world, we can ride the wave of FOMO to maintain momentum, but it’s the “slow and steady” method that helps us weather the crash and deliver that one solid home run.</p> <p>Just Fk**ing Do It.</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>Progress so far:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 54%</li> <li>Data: 12%</li> </ol> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you resonate with the following, let’s chat:</p> <ol> <li>You’re persistent</li> <li>You have dreams</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣3️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 62/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-62-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 62/100days"/><published>2025-04-19T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-19T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-62-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-62-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣2️⃣</p> <p>These past two days, I’ve been watching the first developer competition held by Xiaohongshu, and it got me thinking. I feel like indie developers and indie game developers are quite similar groups. The former probably has a larger population right now, but their survival rate is much lower. It’s a harsh reality—indie game devs can at least build interesting games and monetize directly through one-time purchases. For most indie app developers, though, it’s hard to earn more than what you’d get from a regular job. Some great apps can easily get “honored” by big companies, crushed by competition, or simply die in the early stages. The ones that make it out are rare.</p> <p>It’s kind of surreal. Vibe Coding is becoming more popular now, and you can see a lot of solo devs creating cool apps, but most of them are driven by passion or a desire to create, not profit. B2C is brutally tough; B2B, on the other hand, is very reliant on business skills and connections.</p> <p>This brings up the question: why do so many people still throw themselves into this path? Where do they end up? Maybe I can glimpse a bit of the answer through my own story, though one person’s experience probably doesn’t speak for the majority.</p> <p>I think it’s both a process and an experience. I’ve built many products in the past and provided product development services for individuals and businesses. In my case, the most profitable ones have always been B2B. I wonder if others feel the same. I’ve always had this itch to create (a chronic itch that’s long overdue for treatment), and I keep dreaming of building something truly great. If it brings fame or fortune, even better—that’s part of what keeps driving me to throw myself into new projects.</p> <p>Ironically, I recently stumbled upon an old GitHub and blog intro I wrote:</p> <blockquote> <p>I’m into the internet, traveling, reading, and listening to music – still figuring out this whole “living life” thing.</p> </blockquote> <blockquote> <p>I’m on a mission to balance the grind with some good old-fashioned living.</p> </blockquote> <p>And recently while chatting with a friend, we joked: maybe East Asians just aren’t meant to enjoy life? I genuinely want work-life balance, but my inner workaholic always seems to take over. The most fair thing in life is that everyone gets 24 hours a day. Whenever you invest time and energy in one thing, you’re inevitably sacrificing another. Looking back at the “Life in Weeks” chart I drew in February—from birth to 2077 (my lifespan goal)—maybe now isn’t the time for balance just yet.</p> <p>Today I worked on integrating the map page. I’m currently tweaking the map’s appearance. The default tile layers are ugly and cluttered with too much irrelevant information. I need to simplify and adjust the color scheme. Once that’s done in the next couple of days, I’ll share an update. The goal is to make it silky smooth and visually clean.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 53%</li> <li>Data: 12%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel like you match any of the following, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>You can stick with it</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣2️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 61/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-61-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 61/100days"/><published>2025-04-18T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-18T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-61-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-61-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day6️⃣1️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/3-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/4-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/4-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/4-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/4.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/5-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/5-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/5-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/5.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/6-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/6-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/6-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-18-iter-x-61-100/6.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Map </div> <p>I’m about to start working on the map feature — one of the most crucial aspects of trip planning visualization. For people with a strong sense of direction, like myself, displaying various POIs directly on the map is the most effective way to plan. Personally, once I look at a map and consider my available time and preferences, I can immediately visualize the entire trip’s flow and rhythm.</p> <p>I especially enjoy saving interesting spots on Apple Maps or Google Maps. On the actual travel day, I decide what to visit based on the weather, mood, and time, making flexible decisions on the go. I see this as a nice balance between rigid planning and spontaneous travel. Since I have a good sense of direction and memory for places, I can mentally compute routes or even quickly adjust plans in case of unexpected situations.</p> <p>But I know not everyone shares this habit or ability. What I want to provide is a way to use technology to reduce the cognitive load for people who find this challenging. For example, my partner is the complete opposite — she can’t read maps at all and totally relies on me as her personal GPS. If I can build an app that works well for both of us, I believe it can meet the needs of most people out there.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Frontend (Flutter): 52%</li> <li>Data: 12%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you match any of the following, feel free to reach out and chat:</p> <ol> <li>You can stick with it</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day6️⃣1️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 60/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-60-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 60/100days"/><published>2025-04-17T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-17T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-60-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-60-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day6️⃣0️⃣</p> <p>Today I came across an interesting article called <a href="https://maggieappleton.com/home-cooked-software">Home-Cooked Software and Barefoot Developers</a>. I want to reflect on it a bit and share some of my own thoughts.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/3-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/4-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/4-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/4-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/4.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/5-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/5-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/5-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/5.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/6-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/6-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/6-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/6.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/7-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/7-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/7-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/7.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/8-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/8-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/8-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/8.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/9-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/9-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/9-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/9.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/10-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/10-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/10-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/10.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/11-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/11-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/11-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/11.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/12-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/12-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/12-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-17-iter-x-60-100/12.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Screenshots from the article </div> <p>For a long time, mainstream software products have followed a general-purpose model—once built, they can be used by many people repeatedly. We’ve seen a shift from local applications to cloud-based ones, where data moves to the cloud and devices like phones and computers are just endpoints. Even brain-computer interfaces can be seen as another form of access. In the future, we might see a trend back toward local-first and non-generalized software, partly because of the rise of video coding and AI-assisted development. (Just today I open-sourced a service where over 95% of the work was done by AI—I only handled a few key parts and barely looked at the code.)</p> <p>This means in the future, anyone can build a product, and it doesn’t have to be general-purpose. It could be something made just for a specific event—a trip, a wedding, a one-time activity. It’s disposable, like a single-use item. A generation growing up with such low-cost output tools will naturally adapt to this mindset. The article also mentions that many future products will serve local communities first, which makes perfect sense. The world is not as perfect as the internet makes it seem—there are still huge wealth gaps, underdeveloped regions, and people living below the poverty line. In some ways, AI could help address part of these issues.</p> <p>At the moment, we’re in the industrial, high-modernism age of software, where these standardized, one-size-fits-all apps are made for us by people who don’t know much about us.</p> <p>General-purpose or specialized? Large-scale or small-and-beautiful? Basic needs or long-tail demand? No commercial value = worthless? This article, with just a few slides and brief captions, is really worth a read. Like me, you might find yourself inspired or experience a shift in perspective.</p> <p>It’s like this: for just $20 a month, you can now get a capable assistant who can handle the bulk of development for you. In a way, this is technological inclusion—even long-tail and non-commercial projects now have a chance to exist and matter in the world.</p> <p>Current Progress Overview:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 59%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 51%</li> <li>Data: 12%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel like you match the following, let’s connect:</p> <ol> <li>You’re persistent</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day6️⃣0️⃣]]></summary></entry></feed>