<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-03-18T15:23:52+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ifuryst</title><subtitle>📝 &amp; 💭 </subtitle><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 29/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-29-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 29/100days"/><published>2025-03-17T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-17T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-29-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-29-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣9️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-17-iter-x-29-100/DailyItinerary.2025-03-18_00-11-18-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-17-iter-x-29-100/DailyItinerary.2025-03-18_00-11-18-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-17-iter-x-29-100/DailyItinerary.2025-03-18_00-11-18-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-17-iter-x-29-100/DailyItinerary.2025-03-18_00-11-18.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Daily Itinerary </div> <p>Two new teammates have joined the team, filling the gap in product operations. We also have a C-end product role now—looking forward to future outputs!</p> <p>Today, I focused on handling the AI architecture. It’s mostly sorted out, and tomorrow, I’ll integrate an instance to connect the entire process. On the backend side, we plan to integrate MCP and align with some open-source protocols. MCP itself is an initiative aimed at resolving the chaotic Function Call implementations across different vendors. This should have been something OpenAI led, but since it’s focused on for-profit commercialization, Claude has taken up the mantle. MCP was released last year but has only recently gained traction among developers. Now, various services are starting to build MCP Servers for their platforms. Currently, the only usable client-side applications seem to be Cursor and the Claude app, and an MCP application marketplace is expected to emerge rapidly.</p> <p>If you’re a UI designer, feel free to reach out! Right now, I’m also handling UI design. While I can translate my ideas into designs effectively, we still need a designer with a unique style and vision to elevate the overall design.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 27%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 25%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 7%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, let’s chat! (Maybe check out Day 6 first):</p> <ol> <li>Commitment</li> <li>Dreams</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣9️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 28/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-28-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 28/100days"/><published>2025-03-16T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-16T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-28-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-28-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣8️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-16-iter-x-28-100/TripPage.2025-03-16_23-45-09-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-16-iter-x-28-100/TripPage.2025-03-16_23-45-09-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-16-iter-x-28-100/TripPage.2025-03-16_23-45-09-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-16-iter-x-28-100/TripPage.2025-03-16_23-45-09.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Trip Page </div> <p>This weekend, I’ve mainly been working on the design of the AI architecture. The PR is still in DRAFT status and isn’t fully completed yet; it’s expected to take another two days to finish. In the evenings, I managed to spare some time to refactor and optimize the main itinerary page. It’s still a half-finished project, but over the past month of practice, my understanding of prototype + UI design has improved. However, there’s still a long way to go in terms of aesthetics. I plan to take some time to further develop my taste and artistic sense. I actually get quite anxious when I see others’ designs not aligning with my vision. I think many people feel the same way—most will just say they don’t like something or that it’s not good enough, but they might struggle to pinpoint exactly what’s wrong. I’m really fond of the concept of being a polymath or a learned person, someone who has deep knowledge in a few areas. For an independent creator, it feels like knowing just one thing isn’t enough. You need to have unique insights in several areas to see clearly on the big picture and understand the details as well.</p> <p>Cursor, Windsurf, Claude Code, MCP—if you haven’t been paying attention to these keywords lately, you might want to take note. These are currently trending in the frontier fields, and I’ve been experimenting with applying them in real projects and engineering. There are a lot of thoughts and feelings around this. AI replacing most jobs is definitely not just hype. If you try it seriously, you’ll be disheartened to realize how fragile many professions are under the relentless forward momentum of AI. Based on this, you have to stay on track and not get left behind. Don’t be fooled by the overwhelming Demo-style marketing online. Many exaggerated self-media channels can gradually lull you into complacency. The consequence is that you’ll miss out on new trends simply because you weren’t aware. If you want to exchange ideas or learn about the latest trends in AI, feel free to reach out to me. It’s completely free. I hope to create a small group where we can exchange cutting-edge information, follow relevant papers, news, and startup updates. If you’re interested, feel free to follow me and DM me.</p> <p>Summary of current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 26%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 24%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 6%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (or you can first check out Day 6’s content):</p> <ol> <li>Can persist</li> <li>Has dreams</li> <li>Has interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣8️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 27/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-27-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 27/100days"/><published>2025-03-15T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-15T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-27-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-27-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣7️⃣</p> <p>Today I’ve been focusing on the overall architecture and framework of the AI. The plan is to first implement the PlanAgent and streamline the process, so that the entire framework is thought through and other people can contribute based on this direction. I’m planning to stick to the previous design where we register multiple agents, and each agent can register a series of toolsets. This way, each agent can share tools when handling specific tasks. Currently, agents don’t communicate with each other, because the main goal right now is to integrate AI into the business layer’s various modules. Later, when we have a fully controlled AI, we will extract a main scheduling role in the business layer, where we can consider implementing multi-agent coordination to complete a task. This will also integrate routing gating. Overall, we’ll still follow a multi-layered architecture where the upper layers can repeatedly reuse lower-layer instances, and lower layers are treated as “atomic capabilities” by the upper layers.</p> <p>Summary of the current situation:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 25%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 23%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 6%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (maybe check out Day 6 first):</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣7️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 26/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-26-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 26/100days"/><published>2025-03-14T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-14T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-26-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-26-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣6️⃣</p> <p>Today, I’m not even sure what I did the whole day. In the evening, I was tinkering with other things, and now it’s already 11 PM, only now I have time to look at things. Recently, the question about the future profitability model for the product has come up again. Given that it’s hard to make a profit in the early stages and it requires burning money to support the business, will we be able to survive long enough to build up the user base? It’s a very realistic issue, and that’s why many startups are aiming for a paid app direction. I think building a product itself isn’t that hard; the real challenge comes with the market and operations afterwards. A solid product foundation only helps, but it doesn’t cover up these issues.</p> <p>Aside from that, I think international travel is a relatively less competitive market. Many apps don’t have a sufficiently good product for it. International travel is a growing market, and its scale will continue to expand, making it a worthwhile direction to invest in. However, international travel has a natural disadvantage compared to domestic travel, which is the lower frequency of trips. In the domestic market, we can focus on high-frequency travel, which increases the number of times and frequency that users engage with the app. So I believe it’s essential to combine both, leveraging the strengths of each, to offer a smoother travel experience in one app. Travel is something that lasts a lifetime, and I hope everyone who is physically and mentally on the road can slowly record and leave many memories and mementos. As you travel to more places, you can accumulate and experience more people and things, different encounters. I believe many people don’t or aren’t willing to put in the effort to document their trips through social media, but human memory doesn’t stand up well to the test of time. We may only remember certain things from five years ago, and many of them fade away, lying forgotten in photo albums or videos. Perhaps we can leverage technology and well-thought-out design to deliver a great platform that helps people record every significant journey for the long term.</p> <p>However, vision, ideals, and aspirations need practical support. After climbing high and looking far, we must still walk steadily and take every step seriously. Not everything is about results; the process is something we should enjoy at all times.</p> <p>Travel is never a matter of money but of courage. — Paulo Coelho</p> <p>Back to the beginning, perhaps money isn’t our biggest concern after all—courage is. Knowing when to step back is modern wisdom, and courage to move forward is a unique trait of a traveler’s heart. ❤️</p> <p>Summary of the current status:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 25%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 22%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) progress: 6%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following conditions, feel free to reach out (maybe start by checking out Day 6’s content):</p> <ol> <li>Perseverance</li> <li>Dream</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣6️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 25/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-25-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 25/100days"/><published>2025-03-13T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-13T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-25-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-25-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣5️⃣</p> <p>Today was super fast-paced. I worked on breaking down the product a bit, drew up the architecture diagram, and came up with a preliminary AI solution. We are still going with the FunctionCall+Agent approach, where different functional agents are called via registered tools. There will be two types of tools: one that is adjustable within the program and one that can be invoked during LLM inference. The reason for breaking down the agents into smaller atomic ones is to make them more vertically specialized, allowing for continuous optimization and iteration in specific areas. This will help avoid the problem where optimizing one area causes regressions in another. We can better optimize based on benchmarks for a specific area and improve it. The Routing layer will handle intent recognition or function differentiation to route requests to different agents. This should cover our use cases.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/1.2025-03-14_01-07-13-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/1.2025-03-14_01-07-13-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/1.2025-03-14_01-07-13-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/1.2025-03-14_01-07-13.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/2.2025-03-14_01-07-24-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/2.2025-03-14_01-07-24-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/2.2025-03-14_01-07-24-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/2.2025-03-14_01-07-24.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/3.2025-03-14_01-07-32-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/3.2025-03-14_01-07-32-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/3.2025-03-14_01-07-32-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/3.2025-03-14_01-07-32.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/4.2025-03-14_01-07-38-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/4.2025-03-14_01-07-38-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/4.2025-03-14_01-07-38-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/4.2025-03-14_01-07-38.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/5.2025-03-14_01-07-44-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/5.2025-03-14_01-07-44-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/5.2025-03-14_01-07-44-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/5.2025-03-14_01-07-44.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/6.2025-03-14_01-07-49-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/6.2025-03-14_01-07-49-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/6.2025-03-14_01-07-49-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-13-iter-x-25-100/6.2025-03-14_01-07-49.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Finalized Trip Design Diagram </div> <p>In the evening, I organized and consolidated several pages. The Figma Mirror is really useful. The thickness, font size, spacing, etc., that were previously not designed well are now getting real-time feedback. It’s a “what you see is what you get” process, and the final version was done very quickly. We’ve now locked this version, and both the client and backend can quickly break it down and start working on it. Over the past two days, I’ve realized we need to stick to agile as much as possible. We can’t pursue perfection; it’s better to have something first and iterate. Even if we have to make changes to the pages later due to product shape modifications, the cost won’t be too high, and it’s acceptable. It’s not easy going from 0 to 1, but it’s relatively easier from 1 to 10. Small steps with rapid progress will allow us to reach our MVP by Day 100, or even earlier 🚀. We’ve completed 1/4 of the time, and are we 1/4 of the way there? Overall, we are making progress 🥳.</p> <p>Summary of the current status:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 25%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 22%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) progress: 6%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following conditions, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Can persevere</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Are interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣5️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 24/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-24-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 24/100days"/><published>2025-03-12T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-12T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-24-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-24-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣4️⃣</p> <p>Today I had a chat with ChatGPT and got a cool fact. At least that’s what he said: Octopuses have three hearts. Two hearts are responsible for pumping blood to the gills, and the third heart pumps blood to the rest of the body. And when an octopus swims, the heart that pumps blood to the body stops beating.</p> <p>I thought this was more of a niche fact, haha, but it’s definitely interesting. When I heard him say it, I was a bit taken aback—Octopus, Three Hearts? I double-checked what he said to make sure I wasn’t hearing things. Pretty cool, right? We also talked about Ostriches. Apparently, they’re one of the fastest land animals, capable of running at speeds up to 70 km/h. That’s really fast. In comparison, the fastest land animal, the Cheetah, can only run at 113 km/h for about 20-30 seconds.</p> <p>This year of practicing English has felt like reliving my childhood (from a language-learning perspective). There’s so much you don’t know, so much you don’t know how to ask. It’s like rediscovering knowledge you didn’t pay attention to before. I have to say, AI has completely changed us in every way. It’s like how we talk about FOMO (Fear Of Missing Out)—this kind of emotional state where you’re afraid to miss out on important opportunities, events, or experiences. I think FOMO can be a great motivator, pushing you to keep up and not get left behind in the AI age. I could easily throw out a dozen examples of how AI impacts individuals, companies, and various other areas, but this isn’t an AI class, so I’ll stop here.</p> <p>Our product is also trying to leverage AI to deliver a better, more valuable, human-centered app for travelers and tourists. We really need creative people. You can come in as an advisor to bounce ideas, or you can contribute your talents to change parts of the product. I even think we could treat it like a kind of art piece. We want to succeed commercially, but we’re not just aiming for commercial success. Art-based works inevitably influence the audience, as the work is largely shaped by the creator team. So, I really hope to seek out a diverse team. I believe that someone’s contribution to a team isn’t necessarily measured by the amount of work they do. They can contribute in many ways, and whether someone fits into a team is a two-way process. It’s not easy to find a great team, but we have to keep looking for the right fit. Social platforms give us the chance to discover people, and our reach has gone global beyond just the third-degree connections (in a sense, it’s also the people who love the internet…). It’s a great time to be alive! With more and more people realizing the potential of nonlinear careers or personal development, I hope what I’m sharing here can plant some seeds in your mind. In the future, it might help guide you down a path less traveled, and that might take a lot of courage and awareness. (Maybe it will also give your future self a little push).</p> <p>As you can imagine, when I’m saying all this unrelated stuff, it’s because there isn’t much significant product progress to report 😒. That’s all. See you tomorrow, same time 👋🏼</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 23%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 20%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 5%</li> <li>Data: 5%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to chat:</p> <ol> <li>Persistence</li> <li>Dreamers</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣4️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 23/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-23-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 23/100days"/><published>2025-03-11T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-11T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-23-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-23-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣3️⃣</p> <p>We’ve started preparing to collect points of interest, which will include continents, countries, states, provinces, cities, and specific attractions. There’s quite a large amount of data, and the data team has already been dispatched. The backend team has also begun to provide the corresponding point of interest APIs.</p> <p>The design progress is still a bit slower than expected, and in the next couple of days, I’ll need to align with the product team to finalize some ideas. For now, I’m thinking of releasing early and iterating. Over the next few days, I plan to have the client and backend teams work on some of the pages that are less likely to change significantly, so we can move forward progressively. This week, I’ll also be working on an architecture diagram for the AI side and thinking through the overall flow for AI interaction.</p> <p>Here’s a summary of the current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX Design: 23%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 19%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 5%</li> <li>Data: 5%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣3️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 22/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-22-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 22/100days"/><published>2025-03-10T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-10T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-22-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-22-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣2️⃣</p> <p>Today, I took some time to write code and noticed that I’ve already made 76 commits. I’m really looking forward to finishing the design so I can fully roll out everything. A teammate saw my post from the day before yesterday and told me about a feature in the Figma mobile app — the mirror function. It allows you to cast the page you’re editing on your computer to your phone in real-time. How cool is that! Haha, turns out I was the fool. Most of tonight was spent optimizing details, going through previous pages, and viewing them live on my phone so I could quickly align everything.</p> <p>I originally planned to just let things slide, but then a teammate reached out to me saying they wanted to join us. They wrote me a little essay and mentioned they found me through V2EX and my blog, where they saw the content from the first 21 days. I was actually quite touched. As I shared in my first online meetup, I’m really grateful that I started building in public with a 0/100 mindset. It’s led me to meet so many incredible people with great ideas, and I’ve had a lot of enriching conversations. It feels amazing to know that others believe in my vision and are willing to team up to make it happen. It’s like traveling — the destination isn’t what matters most; it’s the scenery along the way. Just enjoy it, and that’s enough! 🤘</p> <p>BTW, I think one extra benefit of building in public is the dopamine effect. Never underestimate the power of physiology. A lot of people can’t keep going because they don’t understand how to leverage things like dopamine to keep themselves motivated. It’s not about just struggling to persist; it’s about enjoying the process. Knowing how to use your strengths and also boosting them with some inner and external forces to reinforce those strengths. Getting a bit off track here, but anyway, I’m going to sleep. These past few days have been too late, and things are starting to catch fire in the back yard. 🧑🏿‍💻</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype design &amp; UI/UX design: 23%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 18%</li> <li>Mobile client (Flutter): 5%</li> <li>Data: 5%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Can persist</li> <li>Has dreams</li> <li>Is interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣2️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 21/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-21-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 21/100days"/><published>2025-03-09T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-09T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-21-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-21-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣1️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote1.2025-03-09_23-37-23-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote1.2025-03-09_23-37-23-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote1.2025-03-09_23-37-23-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote1.2025-03-09_23-37-23.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote2.2025-03-09_23-37-52-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote2.2025-03-09_23-37-52-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote2.2025-03-09_23-37-52-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote2.2025-03-09_23-37-52.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> 1s Online Meetup Keynote </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote3.2025-03-09_23-38-07-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote3.2025-03-09_23-38-07-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote3.2025-03-09_23-38-07-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote3.2025-03-09_23-38-07.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote3.2025-03-09_23-38-22-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote3.2025-03-09_23-38-22-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote3.2025-03-09_23-38-22-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-09-iter-x-21-100/Keynote3.2025-03-09_23-38-22.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> 1s Online Meetup Keynote </div> <p>Today was the first online meetup, and it went smoothly. Everyone joined in, and we formally got to know each other. The team member from California stayed up until 3 AM to join us 🧑🏿‍💻. We aligned on the vision and ideas behind the product, as well as future plans. Several team members shared what they’ve been working on, and I truly saw the diversity in thoughts. I really liked the following paradigm:</p> <p>Cross-age + Cross-region + Different Experiences + Different Abilities + Ideas + AI = ?</p> <p>We have partners from three different age groups, with various experiences, backgrounds, and regions. Everyone has their own ideas, and at the intersection of the AI era, perhaps something great can spark. The product is just the vehicle, and AI is just the assist; what really makes things happen is turning great ideas into reality in the new context of this era (middle-aged + young people, old ideas + new ideas), and delivering them to people. The long-term value is the key—markets not only need profitable products but products that are valuable and useful to people.</p> <p>To conclude: No app or project will succeed overnight. Enjoy the process, and pursue what you want. There’s no shortcut, just brainpower, persistence, and effort leading to success.</p> <p>Let’s Rock! 🚀</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 23%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 17%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 5%</li> <li>Data: 5%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Ability to persist</li> <li>Dreamer</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣1️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 20/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-20-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 20/100days"/><published>2025-03-08T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-08T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-20-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-20-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣0️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/DesignInIPhone1.2025-03-09_00-39-16-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/DesignInIPhone1.2025-03-09_00-39-16-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/DesignInIPhone1.2025-03-09_00-39-16-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/DesignInIPhone1.2025-03-09_00-39-16.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/DesignInIPhone2.2025-03-08_21-03-05-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/DesignInIPhone2.2025-03-08_21-03-05-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/DesignInIPhone2.2025-03-08_21-03-05-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/DesignInIPhone2.2025-03-08_21-03-05.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Preview design on mobile </div> <p>Today, I discovered a useful design validation tip: open Figma or a screenshot on your phone and zoom in until it matches the size of a phone screen. This way, you can preview the design on your phone ahead of time. It gives a much more intuitive feel than viewing it on a computer. I went through all my pages this way today and found several design issues, especially with font weights, spacing, rectangle sizes, etc. I fixed all the problematic areas. On a large computer screen, everything looks fine because the high-fidelity images can be resized to any comfortable zoom level, but on the phone, it’s much more intuitive. You can immediately spot what doesn’t look right, and your instincts will tell you what needs fixing.</p> <p>I also managed to write a few pages of a PowerPoint because tomorrow is my first meetup. I hope to connect with everyone and take the opportunity to review why I started working on this product, along with some related ideas and features. After the meetup, I’ll be able to share some of the PPT content.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/TripDesign.2025-03-09_00-18-06-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/TripDesign.2025-03-09_00-18-06-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/TripDesign.2025-03-09_00-18-06-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/TripDesign.2025-03-09_00-18-06.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/TimeRangePickerDesign.2025-03-09_00-18-21-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/TimeRangePickerDesign.2025-03-09_00-18-21-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/TimeRangePickerDesign.2025-03-09_00-18-21-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-08-iter-x-20-100/TimeRangePickerDesign.2025-03-09_00-18-21.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Trip Design </div> <p>Yesterday, I scrapped the design of the main itinerary page that I worked on 10 days ago, and today, I scrapped the design I made yesterday. No issues with that! Today, I’ve started to unify the overall style and plan to gradually incorporate a theme color into each page. Without it, everything looks too plain in black and white. If I can integrate some blue into certain areas, it will bring life to the page while maintaining the overall tone.</p> <p>Here’s the current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype design &amp; UI/UX design: 22%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 17%</li> <li>Frontend (Flutter) development: 4%</li> <li>Data: 5%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you fit the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Persistence</li> <li>Ambition</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣0️⃣]]></summary></entry></feed>