<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-05-08T08:45:54+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ifuryst</title><subtitle>📝 &amp; 💭 </subtitle><entry><title type="html">MCP and Its Role in the AI Era—Like HTTP for the Web</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/mcp-vs-http/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MCP and Its Role in the AI Era—Like HTTP for the Web"/><published>2025-05-08T05:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-08T05:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/mcp-vs-http</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/mcp-vs-http/"><![CDATA[<p>Over the past month, the industry has been buzzing:</p> <ul> <li>Two weeks ago, both OpenAI and Amazon announced their adoption of the MCP standard.</li> <li>Last month, Google’s CEO also mentioned on X that they are considering adopting the MCP standard.</li> </ul> <p>Could MCP become the HTTP of the AI era?</p> <p>I think it’s still too early to draw that conclusion. Much of the hype seems to come from social media and industry insiders. However, we can’t ignore the growing trend of MCP adoption. Thanks to media coverage over the past two months, MCP has entered the radar of both technical and non-technical communities.</p> <p>In light of this trend, I’ve started my own exploration—something I’ve always been doing. I’ve noticed that many people have already begun building businesses around MCP application ecosystems. Some MCP Clients, such as Cline, are developing their own App Store-like platforms to make it easier to search for and install MCP Servers. At this stage, most attention is still on MCP Clients. For example, the stdio standard initiated by Anthropic and the use of SSE both lean heavily toward the client side.</p> <p>This makes perfect sense. End-user applications represent a huge opportunity. With the rise of agentic AI, where AIs act as your proxy on the terminal, it’s natural to integrate them directly with your existing environments. This trend is logical and expected.</p> <p>But in areas still underexplored—like remote/cloud/server-side use cases—we will likely see an explosion of applications as well. It’s easy to imagine that the client-heavy approach won’t fit enterprises or more professional users. MCP is not just for terminals. It will be widely used on the server side, in internal enterprise environments, and for external services.</p> <p>I believe traditional FunctionCalling will gradually shift to MCP. Moreover, many existing APIs will need to be adapted to MCP, which will inevitably lead to the emergence of tools and services to support this transition.</p> <p>That’s why I created MCP Gateway—an open-source project I launched in the middle of last month, with the following goals and vision:</p> <ol> <li>Convert existing APIs into MCP Servers through configuration, with zero code changes.</li> <li>Proxy MCP Servers and handle protocol transformations between stdio, SSE, and Streamable HTTP.</li> <li>Act as a unified gateway for distribution—a bold comparison would be the “Nginx of MCP.”</li> <li>Extend into MCP service governance. The imagination space is huge—how do you manage dozens or hundreds of MCP integrations?</li> <li>Deliver enterprise-grade performance, stability, high availability, and scalability.</li> </ol> <p>In just under a week, the project will hit its one-month mark. I’ve made 160 commits, released 13 versions, and gained over 600 🌟 on GitHub. The feedback has been incredibly encouraging, showing me the potential and future applications of this project. I’m continuing to iterate and improve it. You’re more than welcome to try it out, share feedback, or join me in building it together ❤️</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past month, the industry has been buzzing:]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 79/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-79-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 79/100days"/><published>2025-05-06T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-06T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-79-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-79-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣9️⃣</p> <p>After some careful thought, I’ve decided to bring my Build in Public 100 Days series to a close. There are a few key reasons:</p> <p>1️⃣ The number of viewers has steadily declined. I realized that a stream-of-consciousness style isn’t very engaging in the long run.</p> <p>2️⃣ The priority of Iter-X has dropped for me. My other two projects are progressing faster and bringing in more tangible benefits.</p> <p>3️⃣ I’d rather write independent articles moving forward. My current fixed-title format often limits how my better pieces are perceived and makes it harder to reach the right audience.</p> <p>Given all that, I’ve decided to pause this series. Still, I’ve gained so much from the past 79 days — it’s been a rollercoaster, and I’ve made some great connections along the way. More importantly, it’s strengthened my writing ability, and I now feel confident that I can create even better content.</p> <p>For those still following along, feel free to check out my updates on GitHub and my personal blog. I’ll be scaling back how much I share on social media. Instead, I’ll continue posting travel-related content there, while keeping topics like development, product-building, entrepreneurship, personal reflections, and tech/business insights on my blog. Social platforms often limit depth, and I no longer want to compromise on expression.</p> <p>I’ll continue to stay active. I’m not the smartest or most talented person, but I do believe I’m one of the most persistent and action-driven. I’ll keep putting my ideas into motion — regardless of outcome, and without being tied to results alone.</p> <p>The road is long and the mountains high, but I’ll keep walking.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣9️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 78/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-78-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 78/100days"/><published>2025-05-05T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-05T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-78-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-78-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣8️⃣</p> <p>This trip has been incredibly rewarding—not just in terms of rest and relaxation, but also through the unexpected gains that came along the way. That’s part of what travel is about, after all. Though, to be honest, this wasn’t exactly a “regular” trip, since there were plenty of non-travel elements involved as well. I really experienced a lot this time. Fun fact: last night’s reflections were actually written after drinking, and looking back, I wasn’t even drunk—haha.</p> <p>Interestingly, this trip also brought about some unexpected business opportunities. I think they’re quite promising—something like a positive feedback loop for the time and energy I’ve invested into AI over the past year or two. I believe we’re still at the early stage of AI’s penetration across different industries and applications. More and more opportunities will surface. The major players have their own strategies, while smaller players have a completely different playbook. Whether it’s toC, toB, or toG, each path has its own dynamics. I think the people or teams that can integrate capital, technology, distribution, business development, and marketing are the ones who will have a real chance to seize the moment in this wave. Just like the internet boom—it had a lot of hype and bubbles, but also unleashed massive opportunities and created long-tail effects that pushed traditional industries to go digital. The AI era is the same—it may come with bubbles, and some may burst—but the market potential is undeniable.</p> <p>Even though what I write is mostly seen by a small group of tech folks, I remain open-minded and welcome conversations with people from non-technical backgrounds. If you’re in an industry and want to explore using AI to make something happen, feel free to reach out. Whether it’s a quick consultation or the possibility of deeper collaboration, I believe 1+1 can be greater than 2. It’s often the easiest way to create win-win situations.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣8️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 77/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-77-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 77/100days"/><published>2025-05-04T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-04T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-77-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-77-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣7️⃣</p> <p>It was a fulfilling day, non-stop from morning till night. I visited several places, met many people, reflected on life and death, and had deep conversations about the ups and downs of life. Life is just a few decades—it passes quickly. Facing death helps us better reflect on how we truly want to live. Thinking about life’s highs and lows deepens our understanding of the chain reactions caused by key moments in life.</p> <p>Worldly success is something we’ve always chased, but beyond that, there might be deeper things worth pursuing—though often, the former takes priority. Nowadays, many from the new generation are finding spiritual fulfillment as a way to counter material lack, which I see as a sign of progress on a spiritual level. Still, most people find it hard to escape the conventional pattern.</p> <p>Back to routine tomorrow night—everything will gradually return to track, and I’ll keep pushing forward. No pain, no gain — and I’m not done yet.✊</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣7️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 76/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-76-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 76/100days"/><published>2025-05-03T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-03T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-76-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-76-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣6️⃣</p> <p>Every time I go on a trip or immerse myself in a life filled with real-world experiences, the rhythm feels completely different from the usual pace of building things constantly. My mindset shifts significantly.</p> <p>Normally, my focus is on personal growth, consistent output, and the direction and progress of projects and products. In highly social situations, my mental space is taken up by interactions, leaving little room for deep thought. A lot of time gets reallocated to social engagement. During travel, most of my energy goes into experiencing and feeling new things, generating fresh insights and ideas.</p> <p>Personally, I believe all three modes—building, socializing, and traveling—are indispensable. It’s just a matter of how I balance them, which in turn reflects what I value most. While socializing as an adult often emphasizes “meaningful connections,” I still enjoy the occasional spontaneous interaction. It provides a unique perspective and breaks me out of the fixed mindset that often comes with long-term focus on personal projects or commercial success. In that sense, it feels like a form of emotional compensation.</p> <p>Travel is similar. I love traveling not just for the exposure to new experiences and perspectives, but also because different settings allow me to think from different angles. It doesn’t have to be deep—it can be novel and interesting.</p> <p>These past couple of journal entries have felt more like personal diaries, with fewer updates on projects or product development. It feels like the Build in Public series is taking on a different tone now, haha. But I’ll Keep It Real. Regardless of where things stand on Day 100, this has already been a meaningful journey. I hope I can keep up the habit of writing—this positive cycle has noticeably improved both my writing speed and my ability to quickly capture and share ideas. It’s been incredibly helpful for turning input into output.</p> <p>That said, Iter-X’s progress may have disappointed some long-time followers. I’ll take some time after the May Day holiday to reassess.</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Committed</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Curious &amp; interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣6️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 75/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-75-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 75/100days"/><published>2025-05-02T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-02T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-75-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-75-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣5️⃣</p> <p>A busy day—it started early with a morning flight and now I finally have a moment to rest. This year’s May Day travel wave is truly unprecedented. You can tell just from the fully booked flights and the skyrocketing hotel prices, many of which eventually hit full capacity. It’s even more intense than in previous years, clearly reflecting the continued growth of the domestic tourism industry. But it makes me wonder: how long can this trend really last?</p> <p>From a market perspective, such high travel density during holidays seems unsustainable. Yet considering the limited number of holidays in a year, if not during these times, then when can people actually travel? It’s a contradictory situation: the cost of traveling during holidays keeps rising, while the quality of service or travel experience may not be satisfying. So how will consumers choose?</p> <p>Let’s explore some potential solutions:</p> <p>1️⃣ Develop more attractions to spread out visitors: Many regions are already working on this, but building up attractions takes time. Some locations can attract huge crowds through social media hype, but to make that sustainable, supporting services need to keep up.</p> <p>2️⃣ Customized and personalized itineraries: As people visit more destinations, they begin to seek more unique and personalized experiences. This requires professionals in the industry to deeply explore and offer such services. This area is growing, especially in the mid-to-high-end travel market, since profitability allows for better service.</p> <p>3️⃣ Outbound tourism as a form of crowd dispersion: From a national policy standpoint, promoting outbound travel isn’t ideal due to the outflow of spending power. But for individuals and businesses, it’s a lucrative opportunity—offering significantly different experiences at competitive prices can create a win-win for both consumers and providers.</p> <p>4️⃣ Local and nearby travel (an extension of point 1): Encouraging urban or local tourism—like family-friendly countryside retreats—is a good way to retain travelers within their region. These can also attract consistent traffic on regular weekends, which helps boost local consumption and ease holiday congestion.</p> <p>Although the global economy remains sluggish, the tourism industry is experiencing a strong rebound—especially after years of pandemic restrictions. The new generation places greater emphasis on personal experiences and is more willing to invest time and money into meaningful journeys.</p> <p>Current Progress Overview:</p> <ol> <li>UI/UX &amp; Prototype Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend Development (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client App (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data Preparation: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>You’re persistent</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣5️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 74/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-74-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 74/100days"/><published>2025-05-01T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-01T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-74-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-74-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣4️⃣</p> <p>First day of the holiday and I stayed at home, haha. Went out today and witnessed the sheer number of tourists — it was absolutely packed. Despite that, I still managed to release two new versions. High-efficiency output!</p> <p>While I was out, I got inspired with a new idea: an insurance assistant. Right now, due to various reasons, the awareness and acceptance of insurance among many people in China is relatively low. There are several causes, but I believe one major reason is the resistance to salespeople and the headache of trying to understand complex insurance policies. The information gap also leads to major differences in perception. For example, today we encountered a question about whether a 70-year-old can still purchase critical illness insurance, and had to dig through specific policies to find the answer.</p> <p>So I thought — what if we collect policy terms and product data from mainstream insurance companies, and use AI + RAG to build a digital insurance advisor? One that helps users quickly identify suitable products based on their needs, while explaining confusing terms in simple language. This would also help educate the market. From what I know, many insurance agents don’t have strong backgrounds — even though that’s improving, overall professionalism remains uneven.</p> <p>This product could be offered for free, and monetized by partnering with insurance providers — earning commissions when users make purchases through the platform. I think this idea has strong potential for commercialization. I haven’t done formal market research yet (there are probably several competitors already), but I still believe the idea has value. If I choose to pursue it, I’ll likely start by building a version just for myself and close friends, then promote it organically in relevant communities. No monetization in the early phase — just focusing on solving real user pain points. I believe that could lead to a solid user base.</p> <p>Have you ever tried an AI doctor that reads medical reports? I found it extremely helpful. In real life, many doctors don’t have the time or resources to give you thorough explanations. That’s why some patients become experts over time — they’re forced to. AI doctors can fill this gap well. While they might err on the side of caution in diagnosis, they’re great for objective education and personalized health advice. You can ask them step-by-step about a new illness, understand its mechanisms, and learn how your habits might contribute to it. That allows you to take targeted action. I believe the same model could work brilliantly in other vertical domains, including insurance.</p> <p>Of course, building a good product is about removing what doesn’t work, but as a creator or entrepreneur, I think the mindset should be: first identify and amplify what works, then use your ability and resources to fix what doesn’t. Success might not be far from there. These are two different mindsets I often observe. I wonder — which type are you? There’s no absolute right or wrong — just a difference in what suits the path you’re on.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Can stay committed</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Have passion</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣4️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 73/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-73-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 73/100days"/><published>2025-04-30T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-30T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-73-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-73-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣3️⃣</p> <p>Holiday mode has officially begun! My open-source project has hit 571 stars so far — exactly 15 days since launch. Users are starting to integrate it and provide feedback, which I’m really happy about. I’ve set the next milestone at 1k stars, at which point I’ll start working on the Cloud Version, allowing people to configure and experience it directly in the browser. This stage will mostly be free to use.</p> <p>After that, I’ll consider splitting out a commercial version. I haven’t thought too far ahead yet — I’ll decide once we hit the 1k milestone. The commercial edition is part of how I’m thinking about the project’s monetization. It’ll likely include some features that are not in the open-source version. Balancing open-source and commercial offerings is tricky:</p> <ul> <li>If you open too much, the commercial version loses appeal.</li> <li>If you open too little, it hurts adoption and community engagement.</li> </ul> <p>This project has become a great case study in building efficiently in the AI era:</p> <ol> <li>Stay sensitive to gaps in the market</li> <li>Move fast — build and release an MVP in a few days</li> <li>Launch within niche communities to get early feedback</li> <li>Iterate quickly based on real usage</li> </ol> <p>It’s a healthy product loop that fits the AI era perfectly.</p> <p>Looking back at Iter-X, I do feel it’s moving a bit slow — though that’s partly because the to-C (consumer-facing) approach is fundamentally different and demands a higher baseline in terms of stability and design. Still, I’ve learned so much this time around. For example, it’s hard enough to find a solid full-time co-founder — finding reliable collaborators in the part-time pool is even more difficult. Analyzing it this way makes things more understandable.</p> <p>Honestly, building in public has been amazing — it forces you to reflect and consolidate your thoughts. Even if the product I plan to launch on Day 100 doesn’t go live, I’ll have gained a ton of experience and growth just by going through the process.</p> <p>By the way, I’m working on a new idea with a very clear revenue model (already validated in the market). I’m actively doing feasibility research during this holiday break. I might go the solopreneur route for this one. I’m not ready to share details just yet, but if you have strong hands-on experience and deep understanding of AI applications, feel free to reach out. If this idea works out, I’ll need long-term collaborators focused on AI at the application layer.</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>Current progress recap:</p> <ol> <li>UI/UX &amp; prototype design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you check these boxes, come talk to me:</p> <ol> <li>You can commit long-term</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣3️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 72/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-72-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 72/100days"/><published>2025-04-29T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-29T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-72-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-72-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣2️⃣</p> <p>The holidays are coming, and it’s time to get out and explore a bit. It’s been almost three months since I returned from the US for Chinese New Year, and I’ve been working intensely ever since. Time to enjoy some good food and fun.</p> <p>I started this travel app 72 days ago because of my love for traveling—never forget why you started. That said, I really don’t enjoy crowded places; being stuck in a sea of people ruins the experience for me. That’s also why I especially love traveling abroad. I feel many people have the means to travel internationally, but in reality, only a small portion actually go—and even fewer do so consistently.</p> <p>I want to shape this app into a platform for recording life experiences. Right now, most of our memories are scattered across notes, photos, videos, social media posts, and, of course, our minds. But it made me wonder: how do people generally treat their memories? Some people revisit beautiful moments often, some always look ahead, and some fall somewhere in between. I’m in the middle—I rarely scroll back through old photos or videos, but when I see something related, a memory fragment will resurface.</p> <p>Sorting through travel photos and related memories takes a lot of effort, and I believe AI can solve a significant part of that pain.</p> <p>Progress so far:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you fit the following, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣2️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 71/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-71-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 71/100days"/><published>2025-04-28T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-28T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-71-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-71-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣1️⃣</p> <p>Today, an old friend joined to help with the data part. I didn’t expect that someone would join at the final stage of the 100D journey. In the next couple of days, I’ll also review the data scripts written by other teammates. I did a quick test run today — the results look OK, but I haven’t checked the code implementation yet. I’ll work on integrating everything and set it up on the server to start generating some data.</p> <p>Recently, I’ve realized that AI tools like Cursor are much stronger at writing React code than Flutter — you can basically “vibe code” effortlessly with React, but with Flutter, you still often need to manually fix things. I guess this is partly due to the difference in dataset sizes — React (JS) has such a dominant share on GitHub that no other language can easily compete. It’s a bit frustrating. I’m starting to wonder if developing clients with React Native might be faster and smoother. Maybe I’ll try building a small app with it next time and see how it goes.</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Can stay committed</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Have genuine interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣1️⃣]]></summary></entry></feed>