<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-04-11T06:27:29+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ifuryst</title><subtitle>📝 &amp; 💭 </subtitle><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 53/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-53-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 53/100days"/><published>2025-04-10T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-10T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-53-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-53-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 5️⃣3️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-10-iter-x-53-100/rednote-mcp-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-10-iter-x-53-100/rednote-mcp-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-10-iter-x-53-100/rednote-mcp-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-10-iter-x-53-100/rednote-mcp.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> RedNote-MCP </div> <p>Today I spent some time building a RedNote mcp-server using Playwright. It can later be used by agents to fetch note content. Cursor is truly a lifesaver — I even used playwright-mcp to let it navigate pages, extract content, and write code all on its own. Sometimes I just copy an element in the browser and paste it, and it writes the selector automatically. Thinking back to the pre-AI days of using Selenium or Playwright manually was a nightmare — not only did you have to locate elements yourself, but you also had to test thoroughly to make sure everything worked. In this aspect, I really respect AI.</p> <p>When it comes to AI browsing and scraping web content, besides the typical element-based methods like Playwright, here are the common approaches:</p> <p>1️⃣ Directly fetching via URL — this is the easiest to get blocked by anti-scraping systems, since many websites now detect abnormal user behavior.</p> <p>2️⃣ Simulating real user behavior via headless browsers — this is the approach I used earlier. It’s reliable in certain ways and relatively low cost. The downside is that if the page structure or elements change, you need to update your logic.</p> <p>3️⃣ Browser-use powered by vision + LLMs — this is the latest approach. By injecting JS to label interactive elements on the page, LLMs use multimodal reasoning to decide their next move. The biggest pro: it barely requires any manual adjustment, closely mimicking human behavior. The con: it’s expensive.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 53%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter): 42%</li> <li>Data: 12%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>Can stay committed</li> <li>Have a dream</li> <li>Interested and passionate</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 5️⃣3️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 52/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-52-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 52/100days"/><published>2025-04-09T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-09T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-52-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-52-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day5️⃣2️⃣</p> <p>We had an online meeting today to discuss the logic behind data cleaning. The scale of the collected POI (Points of Interest) data is quite large. A complete POI includes basic information such as name, description, address, and coordinates, as well as some value-added information like recommended duration of visit, rating, etc. Some of this data can be collected at scale from public datasets, while the rest needs to be supplemented through other means:</p> <p>1️⃣ Due to the volume, manual work is out of the question initially (although it’s worth noting that manual input can be a viable method—especially at full user scale, users themselves act as data curators, which is the approach many mature platforms take. User-maintained data is often the most accurate).</p> <p>2️⃣ The conventional approach is using web crawlers to gather data from various sources. Some platforms provide this type of data.</p> <p>3️⃣ Nowadays, a lot of this can actually be done with LLMs. We’ve estimated that supplementing one POI consumes roughly 1,000 tokens, so even at the scale of hundreds of thousands of POIs, the cost remains quite low.</p> <p>There’s a lot of nuance in this process, but for now, we’re focusing on the MVP. Optimization can come later.</p> <p>Today, we finally integrated all the Agents, Tools, and Prompts into the database. This will make it easier to manage and switch between different versions. Next, we’ll build a simple admin dashboard for easy management and prompt tuning. We also plan to create a Trajectory Visualization interface for visualizing the Agent call chains, which will make debugging and tracking much more convenient.</p> <p>Current Progress Overview:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 50%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 42%</li> <li>Data: 12%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you match the following, we’d love to talk:</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day5️⃣2️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 51/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-51-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 51/100days"/><published>2025-04-08T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-08T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-51-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-51-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day5️⃣1️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal3-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-08-iter-x-51-100/FigPal3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> FigPal </div> <p>The best part today is FigPal, haha, it’s so cute. It’s a limited-time feature launched by Figma for April Fools’ Day. It’s really a completely useless but fun feature… I really like this kind of nonsense and quirky stuff; it doesn’t have any commercial value, but it’s very helpful for the brand’s tone.</p> <p>Today, I fine-tuned the AI process, and now it’s stable and reliable. It can consistently output itineraries, which I’m very satisfied with. I’m still using the previous pseudo-ToolUse idea, where the AI calls a non-existent tool, create_trip, just to get its stable JSON output. Today, I also discussed some benchmarks and personalization aspects with the AI team, and we’re on the same page. Many of our ideas align well, and in the next few days, I’ll be organizing and setting up a complete set of personalization standards. From our perspective, personalization is divided into two levels:</p> <p>1️⃣ User-level personalization</p> <p>2️⃣ Itinerary-level personalization</p> <p>For example, basic preferences like departure city, return city, departure time, budget, group size, and number of days are all part of the basic preferences. Then there are deeper preferences, like whether you’re more into cityscapes or nature, or whether you prefer a fast-paced trip or a more relaxed one. This hierarchy of preferences, from shallow to deep, can be used with AI to create the most effective itinerary planning assistance. Coming back to the above, user-level preferences are default and can cover all itineraries, but if there are different preferences within the itinerary, they take higher priority and will override the user-level preferences. This makes sense because each trip might be different, whether it’s due to your mood, personal experiences, the people you’re traveling with, the time of year, or the destination. Therefore, this hierarchical structure will be more accurate.</p> <p>Back to user preferences + AI-powered planning, I think there are two main issues in the market right now:</p> <p>1️⃣ The product is not well-done: Many products just mindlessly add AI, but in my opinion, effective planning is far more important than mindless intelligence. I’d rather have AI help once at a critical moment than have the user retry the planning 10 times. AI should have the authority to refuse planning when there’s insufficient information or downgrade to a conservative planning approach—one that works for most users and doesn’t make mistakes. This depends on how well the AI is trained and how well it collaborates with the context.</p> <p>2️⃣ Users have overly high expectations: A lot of people have this problem. AI knows a lot about the world, but it’s not a god. If you ask a regular friend, “I want to travel to Italy for 7 days, help me plan,” do you think their plan will meet all your preferences in one go? Maybe a close friend or family member can do this, but that’s because they have enough understanding of your preferences. So I think it’s important to manage users’ expectations. Otherwise, there’s a risk of overpromising and underdelivering. This is something that all AI product managers should be aware of. Personally, I have some ideas on this. AI can start small, letting users see how it can help in specific situations, and once they develop a basic understanding of its capabilities, the AI can expand to cover more scenarios. This approach is much better than presenting a complete product on a PPT, which might give users high expectations, only for them to experience disappointment when the real product falls short.</p> <p>Lastly, I want to say, if you’re feeling mentally and physically exhausted, don’t push yourself too hard. Take a break to release stress and regain balance. After that, you can jump back in. A long battle won’t be ruined by one or two days, and managing your state is key. When you’re in a good state, your efficiency is higher, and you’ll be more optimistic—otherwise, it’s the opposite.</p> <p>Summary of current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype design &amp; UI/UX design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 45%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) development: 40%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Persistence</li> <li>Dreams</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day5️⃣1️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 50/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-50-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 50/100days"/><published>2025-04-07T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-07T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-50-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-50-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 5️⃣0️⃣</p> <p>The day has finally come — we’ve reached the halfway point. Looking back, 100 days initially felt like they would pass in the blink of an eye. But once the countdown began, I realized how long it truly is. After all, 100 days is almost one-third of a year — basically, an entire quarter. And what you can accomplish in a quarter depends entirely on your mindset.</p> <p>The past couple of days, I’ve been feeling a bit off physically — a little tired, haha. Time to adjust and recharge so I can maintain high energy and efficiency. The road is long and the mountains are high, but I’ll keep moving with my heart.</p> <p>Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 42%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 35%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you believe you match the following qualities, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 5️⃣0️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 49/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-49-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 49/100days"/><published>2025-04-06T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-06T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-49-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-49-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 4️⃣9️⃣</p> <p>Today was insanely busy—I even drove a round trip of 70 kilometers, which took four hours in total. Super packed. A friend also came by to chat about some interesting things, and I really appreciated that. I’m always open to talking with different people. Even though I only have 24 hours in a day, my efficiency and stress tolerance allow me to accomplish a lot—probably more than most people can handle. I’m also very confident that within my capabilities, I can bring different kinds of value to different people.</p> <p>I’ve said this before: more and more people are realizing that the path forward isn’t linear—especially when it comes to career growth. Increasingly, people are seeking nonlinear breakthroughs and returns. I have some of my own experiences and advice to share:</p> <p>1️⃣ First and foremost, you need to build your personal image. Maybe you’re someone great at design, or you’re skilled at building brand identity, or you’re a top-tier tech person. Whatever it is, you need to establish a “persona” for yourself. Of course, this needs to be backed by real skills—otherwise, it’s just a house of cards. Once you start collaborating with others, there’s no room for bluffing.</p> <p>2️⃣ Secondly, don’t act solely out of self-interest. Collaborate with different people and create things together. Through repeated collaboration, you’ll learn more about who you are, meet diverse people, and gradually understand what role you play in a team and what kind of value you bring to the table.</p> <p>3️⃣ Lastly, never stop learning. Strong self-confidence always comes from strong capabilities—or at least strong learning ability. Always stay grounded and confident, ready to take on all the known and unknown challenges ahead.</p> <p>Haha, maybe this is getting a bit lofty and preachy—but hey, it’s all in good fun. I never encourage people to slack off, only to hustle hard. 🤯</p> <p>Current progress update:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 40%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 33%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you match the following, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>You can stick with it</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 4️⃣9️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 48/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-48-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 48/100days"/><published>2025-04-05T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-05T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-48-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-48-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 4️⃣8️⃣</p> <p>Today I’m showing a sneak peek (can’t share the video here~). I’ve progressed to the itinerary creation step, and tomorrow I’ll integrate the previous itinerary page. A small version is starting to take shape. These past two days have been super busy, but very fulfilling. I’ve also been heavily using some AI tools lately — it’s been amazing. I’ll share more when I get the chance.</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype design &amp; UI/UX: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 40%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) progress: 33%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel like you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Committed</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 4️⃣8️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 47/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-47-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 47/100days"/><published>2025-04-04T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-04T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-47-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-47-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣7️⃣</p> <p>The recent popularity of image and video models based on 4.0 has been quite interesting. I admit I’ve also been “experienced” by 4.0, and I believe there are still many aspects where 4.0 cannot match the solutions like ComfyUI + SD. However, I think in most scenarios, it’s the best solution because the barrier to entry is so low. Many people overlook this point, which is incredibly important for a product to reach regular users. It’s crucial to discard the mindset of “this is nothing, *** could already do this” and let go of arrogance and self-righteousness. We need to deeply understand and think about the market and people’s reactions. A product doesn’t need to pursue the most cutting-edge technology to achieve great success. Countless companies and products in history have proven this. We can reflect on why so many people are celebrating, why the design community is panicking and upset, and why OpenAI’s servers are once again unable to handle the pressure. There are profound reasons behind all of this.</p> <p>Riding the wave of this momentum, let me share my thoughts on future startup teams. I think I’ve briefly mentioned this before. I believe future teams will be small and agile, only needing a few key roles:</p> <ol> <li>R&amp;D Personnel: If someone says that a person without any research background can replace this role, I strongly disagree. While Vibe Programming exists, it cannot replace everything. Of course, you can raise funds and hire people once your MVP is out, but fundamentally, you still need someone highly effective in terms of cognition and R&amp;D. Personally, I can now develop several features in half a day, which I would never have imagined before. It used to take me 1 hour to code a feature by hand, but reviewing and making small adjustments now only takes around 10 minutes. The difference in productivity is evident.</li> <li>Product: Excellent product design is something AI cannot fully replace at the moment. It might be a chemical reaction from the subjective irrationality of carbon-based life forms interacting with the real world, including some industry experience. I believe a good idea and a good product direction are the foundation of success. It’s true that anyone can be a product manager, but many products are also just mediocre.</li> <li>Designer: Design is absolutely necessary. AI can do many things, but not everything can be covered by AI. It’s best to have your own unique style and empower it with AI. I actually think design is becoming an even more important role in the future. Although many people worry about being replaced by AI, I see this as a trend, just like how AI may eventually replace R&amp;D personnel. However, there are higher-level elements that human designers can offer, which act as their moat.</li> <li>Operations: A product requires ongoing operations. A key point in operations is having a style and knowing various operational strategies. We can let AI help with operational materials, but the actual implementation still needs people with sufficient cognition and experience.</li> <li>Business Growth: This is a crucial area. AI can’t help you with business, at most it can help you write a business plan, but it can’t help you find investors, pitch your ideas, or think about business growth based on actual situations. In fact, I think business is one of the areas where AI currently has the least impact.</li> </ol> <p>Perhaps in the future, teams will only need five “superheroes.” If you find that the people in your team can’t use AI, you might want to be cautious. Of course, I don’t oppose Old School; I think it can be a form of sentiment ❤️</p> <p>I still like my key point: AI can’t help you stay persistent, it can’t help you always stay motivated. The only thing that can stop you from moving forward is your heart and your comfy sofa 😇</p> <p>Summary of current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 39%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 30%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Can persist</li> <li>Has dreams</li> <li>Is interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣7️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 46/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-46-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 46/100days"/><published>2025-04-03T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-03T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-46-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-46-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣6️⃣</p> <p>I’ve adjusted the AI again. I’m planning to use Function Call’s JSON return to achieve a stable structured JSON output. Essentially, I’m tricking the AI by using a tool that doesn’t actually exist or need execution. Normally, we rely on prompts to request a JSON response, but that approach doesn’t seem to guarantee 100% stability.</p> <p>I’ve also further broken down the agents into more atomic units. Now, each agent handles a very specific task, making it easier to reuse their functions. For example, I’ve separated CityPlanner and TripPlanner, so if the destination city is unknown, AI can first plan the cities before diving into the itinerary. Over the next couple of days, I’ll focus on connecting the entire itinerary module, which will bring the core functionality to life.</p> <p>It’s hard to believe that nearly half of the 100-day journey has passed. The intensity of daily output is quite demanding, especially since some days don’t show obvious progress. The public is mostly visual-oriented, and I don’t want to dig into too many technical details because that would be even more tedious. Instead, I mix in insights and news occasionally. If I build in public again in the future, I might consider sharing in phases rather than posting daily updates. I don’t want the content to become a monotonous log—I’d rather deliver it when there’s something valuable to share.</p> <p>Current Progress: • Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33% • Backend (Go) Development: 36% • Client (Flutter) Development: 25% • Data: 10%</p> <p>If you meet the following criteria, let’s connect:</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Ambitious</li> <li>Passionate</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣6️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 45/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-45-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 45/100days"/><published>2025-04-02T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-02T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-45-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-45-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣5️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePageSkeleton-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePageSkeleton-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePageSkeleton-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePageSkeleton.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePage-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePage-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePage-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePage.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Main Trip Page &amp; Mine Page </div> <p>Still working on the pages. I plan to integrate the itinerary this week and check if I’m going anywhere for the Qingming Festival. If not, I should be able to finish it. The progress has been good these past two days. I will reassess the overall progress next week. These tasks are being pushed forward based on my intuition, not following a strict timeline, which I think is one of the challenges in project management. If there was a clear roadmap and the requirements were well-defined, progress could be more predictable and manageable. Otherwise, it’s difficult to smoothly advance the project. Right now, we’re still in a chaotic state, and everything is growing wildly, which is a significant issue. However, we could consider introducing a simple visual dashboard to track our MVP progress. But because the collaboration is quite loose, it’s challenging to bring in project management tools commonly used in the industry. This is a bit of a paradox, and I’ll need to think about and learn more about it. The goal is not to add unnecessary complexity, but to make sure everyone on the team clearly understands the current project status—where the bottlenecks are, where they stand, and what others are working on. These insights would be meaningful.</p> <p>Here’s the current summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 34%</li> <li>Frontend (Flutter) progress: 23%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we need a UI designer 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dreamer</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣5️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 44/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-44-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 44/100days"/><published>2025-04-01T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-01T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-44-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-44-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣4️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/cursor-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/cursor-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/cursor-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/cursor.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> POI </div> <p>Today, we made significant progress with our POI data. Our new team member has been incredibly helpful, successfully running the data source and processing many POI records. In three days, after another team member who is currently traveling returns, we’ll review the ETL logic, and we can begin the data cleaning process.</p> <p>I spent the day immersed in n8n workflow orchestration. There are some tasks I can automate using n8n, which will help improve my efficiency and productivity. I think investing time in this is worthwhile. For example, I can quickly push articles I’ve written to different platforms through some custom nodes and workflows. Another thing is information aggregation and dimensionality reduction. I’ve been consuming a lot of information daily, and I need to aggregate it to reduce redundant news. This way, I can allocate more time to reading in-depth articles. Having a broad yet precise strategy allows me to stay on top of the latest trends while also exploring interesting ideas. I’ll share more on this topic later.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/poi-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/poi-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/poi-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/poi.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Cursor </div> <p>I also saw Anysphere, the startup behind Cursor. They expect to generate $200 million in Annual Recurring Revenue (ARR) through subscriptions over the next 12 months. They’re currently raising a new round of funding, and their valuation is expected to reach $10 billion. This company currently has only 50 employees, which is impressive. Their success is largely due to early popularity within developer circles and winning Product Hunt’s 2024 Product of the Year award. Since then, they’ve continued to gain popularity. Their net revenue retention rate (NRR) for March 2024 reached an astounding 250%. What does this mean? It indicates that their existing customers are not only continuing to pay but are also paying more—$1 per customer is now $2.50. A typical NRR of 115% is already considered excellent, as it signifies steady revenue growth from existing customers. So, Cursor’s NRR is truly remarkable. Personally, I’m not surprised at all. I think Cursor has surpassed traditional IDEs and has become the new standard. JetBrains products seem to have stagnated. Recently, I’ve been using it extensively for creating SOP manuals and training documents for my team to refer to before starting new tasks. The results have been incredible. One of my team members, whom I introduced to it, couldn’t stop praising it and spent the entire day watching AI-related content. I’ll share more on this topic later. If you’re still in the camp of not using it or criticizing it as hard to use, I urge you to reconsider. I believe you’ll soon realize that others are moving ahead, and if you think it’s hard to use, try to see if you’re using it incorrectly or misjudging the AI’s capabilities, leading to incorrect results. Don’t let simple biases stop you from learning and mastering new things.</p> <p>Current Progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 34%</li> <li>Frontend (Flutter) Progress: 21%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you fit the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we’re looking for a UI designer 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dreamer</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣4️⃣]]></summary></entry></feed>