<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-04-30T16:13:13+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ifuryst</title><subtitle>📝 &amp; 💭 </subtitle><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 73/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-73-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 73/100days"/><published>2025-04-30T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-30T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-73-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-73-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣3️⃣</p> <p>Holiday mode has officially begun! My open-source project has hit 571 stars so far — exactly 15 days since launch. Users are starting to integrate it and provide feedback, which I’m really happy about. I’ve set the next milestone at 1k stars, at which point I’ll start working on the Cloud Version, allowing people to configure and experience it directly in the browser. This stage will mostly be free to use.</p> <p>After that, I’ll consider splitting out a commercial version. I haven’t thought too far ahead yet — I’ll decide once we hit the 1k milestone. The commercial edition is part of how I’m thinking about the project’s monetization. It’ll likely include some features that are not in the open-source version. Balancing open-source and commercial offerings is tricky:</p> <ul> <li>If you open too much, the commercial version loses appeal.</li> <li>If you open too little, it hurts adoption and community engagement.</li> </ul> <p>This project has become a great case study in building efficiently in the AI era:</p> <ol> <li>Stay sensitive to gaps in the market</li> <li>Move fast — build and release an MVP in a few days</li> <li>Launch within niche communities to get early feedback</li> <li>Iterate quickly based on real usage</li> </ol> <p>It’s a healthy product loop that fits the AI era perfectly.</p> <p>Looking back at Iter-X, I do feel it’s moving a bit slow — though that’s partly because the to-C (consumer-facing) approach is fundamentally different and demands a higher baseline in terms of stability and design. Still, I’ve learned so much this time around. For example, it’s hard enough to find a solid full-time co-founder — finding reliable collaborators in the part-time pool is even more difficult. Analyzing it this way makes things more understandable.</p> <p>Honestly, building in public has been amazing — it forces you to reflect and consolidate your thoughts. Even if the product I plan to launch on Day 100 doesn’t go live, I’ll have gained a ton of experience and growth just by going through the process.</p> <p>By the way, I’m working on a new idea with a very clear revenue model (already validated in the market). I’m actively doing feasibility research during this holiday break. I might go the solopreneur route for this one. I’m not ready to share details just yet, but if you have strong hands-on experience and deep understanding of AI applications, feel free to reach out. If this idea works out, I’ll need long-term collaborators focused on AI at the application layer.</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>Current progress recap:</p> <ol> <li>UI/UX &amp; prototype design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you check these boxes, come talk to me:</p> <ol> <li>You can commit long-term</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣3️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 72/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-72-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 72/100days"/><published>2025-04-29T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-29T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-72-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-72-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣2️⃣</p> <p>The holidays are coming, and it’s time to get out and explore a bit. It’s been almost three months since I returned from the US for Chinese New Year, and I’ve been working intensely ever since. Time to enjoy some good food and fun.</p> <p>I started this travel app 72 days ago because of my love for traveling—never forget why you started. That said, I really don’t enjoy crowded places; being stuck in a sea of people ruins the experience for me. That’s also why I especially love traveling abroad. I feel many people have the means to travel internationally, but in reality, only a small portion actually go—and even fewer do so consistently.</p> <p>I want to shape this app into a platform for recording life experiences. Right now, most of our memories are scattered across notes, photos, videos, social media posts, and, of course, our minds. But it made me wonder: how do people generally treat their memories? Some people revisit beautiful moments often, some always look ahead, and some fall somewhere in between. I’m in the middle—I rarely scroll back through old photos or videos, but when I see something related, a memory fragment will resurface.</p> <p>Sorting through travel photos and related memories takes a lot of effort, and I believe AI can solve a significant part of that pain.</p> <p>Progress so far:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you fit the following, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣2️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 71/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-71-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 71/100days"/><published>2025-04-28T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-28T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-71-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-71-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣1️⃣</p> <p>Today, an old friend joined to help with the data part. I didn’t expect that someone would join at the final stage of the 100D journey. In the next couple of days, I’ll also review the data scripts written by other teammates. I did a quick test run today — the results look OK, but I haven’t checked the code implementation yet. I’ll work on integrating everything and set it up on the server to start generating some data.</p> <p>Recently, I’ve realized that AI tools like Cursor are much stronger at writing React code than Flutter — you can basically “vibe code” effortlessly with React, but with Flutter, you still often need to manually fix things. I guess this is partly due to the difference in dataset sizes — React (JS) has such a dominant share on GitHub that no other language can easily compete. It’s a bit frustrating. I’m starting to wonder if developing clients with React Native might be faster and smoother. Maybe I’ll try building a small app with it next time and see how it goes.</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Can stay committed</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Have genuine interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣1️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 70/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-70-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 70/100days"/><published>2025-04-27T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-27T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-70-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-70-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 7️⃣0️⃣</p> <p>Today, I officially launched my open-source project on Product Hunt. The Day 1 campaign will begin tomorrow, April 28th, at 3 PM Beijing time. I’m hoping to make a strong push for the charts! In just 12 days, I made 107 commits and released version v0.2.7. Before the era of generative AI, achieving something like this would have been almost unimaginable — nearly impossible. It’s a powerful reminder of how fast the world is moving forward, and how individuals are swept along, willingly or not, running ever faster.</p> <p>As Dickens famously said, “It was the best of times, it was the worst of times…” — just like everything has two sides, it all depends on how you choose to look at it. Personally, I believe it’s the best of times — an era that grants individuals unprecedented “capabilities” and acceleration. Unlike the internet era, which didn’t go through a chaotic early stage, the AI era has brought a real, palpable sense of chaos — but with it, an ever-expanding space for imagination and intensity.</p> <p>I’ll be slowing down Iter-X development for the next couple of days. I expect to resume full momentum after the May 1st holiday, as I have some other commitments coming up. In the meantime, I’ll continue sharing thoughts and experiences.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Development: 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel you match the following criteria, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>You have perseverance</li> <li>You have dreams</li> <li>You have passion</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7️⃣0️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 69/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-69-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 69/100days"/><published>2025-04-26T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-26T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-69-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-69-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣9️⃣</p> <p>I suddenly remembered one of the reasons why I started this 100 Days Build in Public challenge: Simon Willison.</p> <p>He’s an incredibly prolific writer. One time he talked about how he manages to be so productive, and he mentioned that he once did 100 consecutive days of content creation. Combined with his years of writing experience, he can now quickly turn the information he absorbs into writing every day, maintaining a high-output state. This idea stuck with me, and that night, on a bit of an impulse, I decided to give it a try myself.</p> <p>The “power of 100” is real — once you go through it, you truly experience all the ups and downs. I think it’s worth doing at least once. It’s like a burst of impulsive passion or impulse spending — only through time and real experience can you grasp the real sweetness and bitterness of it.</p> <p>Although I’ve always believed that frontend or client-side work is more visible — easier to show results — while backend work (especially in the early stages) often looks like simple CRUD operations until it reaches a certain scale, I’ve realized that doing frontend or client development is actually incredibly demanding and often underappreciated. If you really want to pursue a perfect experience and polish the presentation, it requires a massive amount of time and energy. From my past experience, frontend and client-side work usually consumes a disproportionate amount of effort — maybe because I’m not a seasoned frontend or mobile engineer.</p> <p>Now, with tools like Cursor + ChatGPT, many things are easier to cover, but the real challenge lies in continuous tuning and testing. Many times, you think you’ve communicated your idea clearly, but the actual result can turn out quite different.</p> <p>Today, I finished polishing some basic add/delete functionalities. Even for a seemingly simple page, the information density is very high, and what it requires is built up layer by layer.</p> <p>Here’s a summary of my current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend Development (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client-side Development (Flutter): 58%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel you fit the following, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Can stay consistent</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Have passion and interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣9️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 68/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-68-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 68/100days"/><published>2025-04-25T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-25T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-68-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-68-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day6️⃣8️⃣</p> <p>As expected, having influential people with strong traffic help promote the project had a great impact, leading to a rapid boost. However, the key lies in choosing the right direction and track — only then can others immediately recognize the quality of your project. Choosing the right track and then working hard is crucial.</p> <p>Speaking of which, Iter-X’s problem lies in its business model. Actually, I kind of want to ask Junyu Wang what he thinks about this [DOGE]. His project, “Reading Room,” shows a similar shadow to what I’m experiencing. I don’t know how he thought through his product; I’ve only seen glimpses of his journey through his articles. Somehow, I feel a one-sided resonance with him — seeing a bit of myself in his experiences. Of course, it’s just a thought; I don’t really have a way to reach out to him.</p> <p>I feel that from these couple of days until after May 1st, my project progress might slow down significantly. In a way, the next month looks pretty unpredictable. I’ve been considering whether I should shift to building a long-term cycle product. After nearly 100 days of high-intensity push — almost a 007 (work-life blend) commitment to this side project — I’m thinking about finding a better balance, especially since I’m not “all-in” on a single project.</p> <p>Recently, I’ve also had some new ideas about the product positioning. Perhaps this project can evolve toward the form of products like Devin or Manus, but with a strong focus on the travel field. It would allow for a gradual, progressive functional layering. Though this idea is not fully matured yet.</p> <p>I’ll keep absorbing a large amount of information, working on entropy reduction, and see what might eventually come out of it. 🙂</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend Development (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client Development (Flutter): 57%</li> <li>Data Preparation: 14%</li> </ol> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you think you fit the following profile, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Able to stay persistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day6️⃣8️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 67/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-67-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 67/100days"/><published>2025-04-24T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-24T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-67-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-67-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣7️⃣</p> <p>Marketing is crucial, especially in the early stage of a project. My two recent open-source projects both gained initial momentum by being shared in the right circles and platforms. They got in front of the right audience from day one. Then it’s all about expanding exposure—getting your product or project seen in more places. Even if it doesn’t attract attention immediately, it can have a long-term effect. People will gradually trickle in. What you need to do is keep iterating.</p> <p>Even though these are just open-source projects, the approach is essentially a PMF (Product-Market Fit) journey. I’m learning a lot through this:</p> <p>1️⃣ Good wine still needs marketing. A great idea may go unnoticed if you don’t know how to market it—and you might miss the window of opportunity.</p> <p>2️⃣ Sometimes you’re not sure if your idea is actually a good one. But if someone gives you that initial validation, it can make a huge difference. And even if the first idea isn’t the one, it might evolve into something powerful. Often, you don’t realize its potential until later.</p> <p>3️⃣ Speed is everything, especially in the age of AI. I keep telling my friends this: if you have an idea, just do it. Even a one-week delay might cost you the moment. The goal isn’t to build something perfect—it’s to go from 0 to 1. You’ll likely get something valuable out of it.</p> <p>4️⃣ Build your own distribution channels. Think of yourself as the maker—but also the distributor. Channels matter.</p> <p>That’s about it. Easier said than done, but action speaks louder than words. By the way, someone influential tagged my project today. 🤞 Hope it brings more visibility by this Friday.</p> <p>Honestly, I’ve been treating this #100Days challenge like writing a diary, haha. The truth is, I can’t always produce solid progress every single day. Sometimes my commits aren’t full features or polished modules. People are visual creatures—I get that. I’m not breaking things down into technical pieces on purpose. Also, I’m not a content creator, so I don’t have the skills to “cook up” flashy updates. I just share my thoughts and recent learnings—freely and casually.</p> <p>Current progress: • Prototype design &amp; UI/UX: 33% • Backend (Go): 60% • Client (Flutter): 57% • Data: 14%</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you match any of the following, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>You’re consistent</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣7️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 66/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-66-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 66/100days"/><published>2025-04-23T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-23T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-66-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-66-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣6️⃣</p> <p>Not much progress today. I’ve been heavily focused on MCP lately, and also experimenting with travel planning done directly via unwrapped LLMs. It gave me some new ideas for the product. I’m starting to believe that the moat for this type of travel planning product might lie in data:</p> <p>1️⃣ First, having a reliable and objective factual dataset can significantly suppress hallucinations and maximize the user experience. This is also a key reason why RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) is so popular. I think many LLM-based vertical products can actually be classified as RAG applications.</p> <p>2️⃣ Second, user data. With ChatGPT’s new Memory feature, I think we’re witnessing a real game-changer. Making users feel “wow, this thing gets me” relies entirely on user data + data generated during usage.</p> <p>For products in this specific category, different monetization models will highlight different strengths — for example, some might compete based on their supply chain. Just some food for thought.</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 56%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>If you feel like you fit the following description, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>You can stay committed</li> <li>You have a dream</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣6️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 65/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-65-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 65/100days"/><published>2025-04-22T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-22T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-65-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-65-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣5️⃣</p> <p>Amap’s support for Flutter is honestly pretty disappointing — the latest version (3.0.0) is still from three years ago. Feels kinda rough. For now, I’ll make do with it and figure out a better solution later. The basic map rendering is more or less done. Currently, I’m using a simple “Day.N” format to represent point-to-point routes. In the future, I’ll replace those with POI stickers. Up next is adding functionality to insert and remove stops in the itinerary. After that, I’ll move on to the expense tracking module.</p> <p>Time really flies. Things have been pretty hectic lately, and progress has slowed down a bit. On top of that, a lot of teammates have been walking away one by one. It’s a familiar scene — in the end, it’s rare to find people who truly walk the whole path with you. And that’s okay. I’ll tweak things and keep pushing forward.</p> <p>Also, I recently open-sourced two AI-related projects, which got a lot of love from developers. I’m planning to carve out some dedicated time to grow one of them into a full-fledged SaaS service. That said, I’ll still keep iterating on Iter-X. I’m just not sure if the original milestones can still be hit on time. But since I’ve set off on this path, there’s no turning back — this is the commitment and perseverance needed to walk a road less traveled.</p> <p>Mentally, I feel pretty great every day. Physically, though, my carbon-based body is having trouble keeping up. I went for my first swim of the year this afternoon, and I plan to swim twice a week moving forward. Gotta keep my body in shape to keep the output going strong. It’s late now — good night!</p> <p>⸻</p> <p>Current Progress Overview:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 56%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you match the following traits, feel free to reach out:</p> <ol> <li>Consistent</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Passionate</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣5️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 64/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-64-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 64/100days"/><published>2025-04-21T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-21T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-64-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-64-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day 6️⃣4️⃣</p> <p>Immersed in a sea of data, endlessly exploring. Today I’ve been calibrating the transformation from WGS84 to GCJ02 coordinate systems. Some of the previous data had location inaccuracies, so I’m adjusting the logic to fix it. Hopefully I can finish refining the scripts this week and start large-scale POI processing. Related images are also being crawled, and will later be uploaded in batches to OSS.</p> <p>When dealing with images and videos, the two most costly factors are usually: 1. Storage and 2. Bandwidth. Storage tends to be cheaper, and we can optimize costs by implementing cold/hot storage separation. But bandwidth is where costs can spiral, so we pay extra attention there.</p> <p>Typically, we generate several thumbnail versions of each image. In most cases, a thumbnail of just a few dozen KB is sufficient, especially on mobile screens. With lossless compression, we can reduce file sizes of high-res images significantly. And we can even sacrifice some resolution without noticeable impact to the human eye — unless you zoom in. That’s why we strike a balance between visual quality and cost by generating a few common thumbnail sizes.</p> <p>Some systems even support on-the-fly image resizing via URL parameters. This avoids the need to store multiple versions, though it requires generating images in real-time. However, if paired with a CDN, you only need to generate the image on the first request, which is totally acceptable. There’s no silver bullet — only solutions that best match your scenario and budget.</p> <p>Progress so far:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go): 60%</li> <li>Client (Flutter): 55%</li> <li>Data: 14%</li> </ol> <p>⸻</p> <p>If you identify with the following, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>You’re persistent</li> <li>You’ve got dreams</li> <li>You’re genuinely interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 6️⃣4️⃣]]></summary></entry></feed>