<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-03-24T16:02:40+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ifuryst</title><subtitle>📝 &amp; 💭 </subtitle><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 36/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-36-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 36/100days"/><published>2025-03-24T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-24T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-36-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-36-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣6️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App.TestFlight-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App.TestFlight-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App.TestFlight-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App.TestFlight" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App1.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App3-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-24-iter-x-36-100/App3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> App TestFlight </div> <p>Today I organized the client app’s icons, name, and such, and also sent it out on TestFlight. Over the next couple of days, I’ll focus on infrastructure, and then we can start pushing the pages.</p> <p>I feel that the loose collaboration style is not ideal. It’s already difficult to find people who can stick with it, and with part-time work, everyone’s time and energy are unpredictable. On top of that, continuous input is needed, which really filters out most people. But I think this is an interesting phenomenon. This is my first time trying to attract others through social media. Watching everyone’s evolution from initial idea exchanges to different behaviors as time goes on has been a fascinating process. I think this kind of collaboration, combining open-source principles with social platforms, is very dynamic and helps with learning. It further validates my idea that entrepreneurship can’t just rely on close relationships; you can’t naively assume that your good friends are the best people to work with. Instead, you should look for that “one in a million” person. Perhaps this also indirectly explains why there are more solo entrepreneurs — finding the right partners is not easy. Is this a bit pessimistic? I’m still optimistic. I have a strong ability to balance my own emotions and pressures. When you want to attract and lead others toward a distant future, you need to be strong enough to handle most situations. When everyone else falls, you still have to stand. If you don’t have this mindset, then just close your laptop and enjoy a 9-to-5 job, balancing life and work. No need to burn your life doing something you don’t enjoy.</p> <p>Recently, I’ve been thinking about exploring further how AI can help improve my efficiency and productivity. A lot of what’s online is just demo-style sharing, but I’m looking for something practical that can actually assist. If you know about this and are willing to share, feel free to DM me 🚀</p> <p>Summary of current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype design &amp; UI/UX design: 30%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 30%</li> <li>Client app (Flutter) progress: 12%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we’re looking for a UI design partner 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Able to stick with it</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣6️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 35/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-35-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 35/100days"/><published>2025-03-23T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-23T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-35-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-35-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣5️⃣</p> <p>Today, I merged some parts of the client, and I did a little testing. It seems that the progress on the client side is still not quite enough. Over the next few days, I’ll dedicate some effort to addressing issues on the client side and also fill in the gaps on the backend API. The design work might be a little slower as a result.</p> <p>Here’s an overview of the current status:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 30%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 30%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 10%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to chat with me (we’re looking for a UI design partner 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Perseverance</li> <li>Dreamer</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣5️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 34/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-34-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 34/100days"/><published>2025-03-22T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-22T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-34-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-34-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣4️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-22-iter-x-34-100/POIsPicker.2025-03-22_23-44-01-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-22-iter-x-34-100/POIsPicker.2025-03-22_23-44-01-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-22-iter-x-34-100/POIsPicker.2025-03-22_23-44-01-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-22-iter-x-34-100/POIsPicker.2025-03-22_23-44-01.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> AI for Trip Planing </div> <p>A friend sent me a smart planning feature from Gaode. You input “3-day trip to Hangzhou,” and it starts planning. It even outputs the reasoning process of the model. I suddenly felt a bit absurd – the user just entered these five words, and AI is already thinking? It feels almost magical. It doesn’t even ask for user preferences. Is this kind of forced reasoning really thinking? I feel like many product teams today are missing the point. It’s like the famous story of Steve Jobs talking to his engineers. Today, many teams make the same mistake: they prioritize technology over product. Essentially, it’s “AI first.” In reality, we should start from the user. Only then should we think about whether this technology is needed, where it’s needed, to what extent, and what it can achieve. This is the logical direction to consider. Of course, I understand that FOMO, KPIs, and other pressures can lead to this approach, but just because it’s “necessary” doesn’t mean it’s the right approach.</p> <p>I even think we should let AI have a certain attitude. For instance, if you provide too little information, we shouldn’t recommend anything. Because it’s easy to recommend incorrectly, and the outcome could be: 1) The user feels like it doesn’t work and quits. 2) The user manually deletes the recommendation. 3) Or the user keeps asking AI to optimize it. Essentially, we’re wasting computational power, which equals burning money to satisfy unclear needs, guessing user preferences in a labor-intensive way, which is not productive.</p> <p>If we must force AI to recommend based on such limited information, that’s fine. We can go with a safer, more generic approach. This can meet the needs of the majority of users, especially those visiting a place for the first time. The chances are they will want to see the more famous attractions.</p> <p>Another point is that recommendations need to be justified. The reason for recommending a specific POI should be clear to the user because users have the final decision. For example, when browsing travel spots on platforms like Xiaohongshu or social media, you don’t visit all the top 10 places. You will only go to those that interest you. The key is understanding why something interests you.</p> <p>I still think we need to return to the original goal: start with a useful itinerary planner, then make it smarter. Many products today only focus on a direction or a few points, but what users expect is a complete product. We want to deliver this complete product. Now, I actually feel happier and lighter because the real concern for me was the financial pressure AI would bring. If we can get our approach right, maybe we don’t need such high upfront costs to validate whether the market believes in our vision.</p> <p>Current status summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 29%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 30%</li> <li>Frontend (Flutter) progress: 8%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we need a UI design partner👾):</p> <ol> <li>Persistence</li> <li>Ambition</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣4️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 33/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-33-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 33/100days"/><published>2025-03-21T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-21T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-33-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-33-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣3️⃣</p> <p>No significant progress updates today—I’m still evaluating options for full-text search and haven’t finished yet. I’ve realized that when working part-time, doing a 100-day continuous progress update can sometimes turn into a routine log, so I’ll try to avoid that.</p> <p>I’m planning to host an AI sharing session this weekend. Some teammates are interested in AI but don’t have much exposure, so I’ll go over the current state of AI, possible developments this year, and real-world applications. If you’re interested, feel free to DM me.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 28%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 30%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 8%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, let’s talk! (We’re looking for a UI designer 👾)</p> <ol> <li>Committed</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Passionate</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣3️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 32/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-32-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 32/100days"/><published>2025-03-20T15:00:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-20T15:00:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-32-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-32-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣2️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-20-iter-x-32-100/AI4TripPlaning.2025-03-20_22-59-27-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-20-iter-x-32-100/AI4TripPlaning.2025-03-20_22-59-27-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-20-iter-x-32-100/AI4TripPlaning.2025-03-20_22-59-27-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-20-iter-x-32-100/AI4TripPlaning.2025-03-20_22-59-27.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> AI for Trip Planing </div> <p>The AI architecture and overall framework are complete, and an intelligent itinerary creation process is now running successfully. However, there are still some tasks to tackle:</p> <ol> <li>Consider integrating MCP for further standardization.</li> <li>Enhance observability—LLM calls need monitoring, including cost tracking, input-output sampling, etc., to support future Agent version iterations with data.</li> <li>Strengthen boundary handling to ensure fallback mechanisms in certain scenarios.</li> <li>Standardize prompt version management.</li> <li>Optimize full-text search—consider replacing Elasticsearch with Postgres, which should be sufficient for a long time.</li> <li>Improve Agents and Tools.</li> </ol> <p>These tasks can be addressed progressively. Now that the framework is in place, AI engineers can focus on optimization, backend developers can implement logic, and data engineers can integrate data.</p> <p>Current Progress:</p> <ul> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 28%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 30%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 8%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ul> <p>🚀 We’re looking for a UI designer! If you meet the following criteria, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>Committed</li> <li>Ambitious</li> <li>Passionate</li> </ol> <p>Let’s build something amazing together! 👾</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣2️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 31/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-31-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 31/100days"/><published>2025-03-19T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-19T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-31-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-31-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣1️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-19-iter-x-31-100/Map1.2025-03-20_00-18-07-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-19-iter-x-31-100/Map1.2025-03-20_00-18-07-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-19-iter-x-31-100/Map1.2025-03-20_00-18-07-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-19-iter-x-31-100/Map1.2025-03-20_00-18-07.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-19-iter-x-31-100/Map2.2025-03-19_23-55-22-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-19-iter-x-31-100/Map2.2025-03-19_23-55-22-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-19-iter-x-31-100/Map2.2025-03-19_23-55-22-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-19-iter-x-31-100/Map2.2025-03-19_23-55-22.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Map </div> <p>Today, I imported some POI data and conducted a full-text search. Tomorrow, I’ll continue working on the AI workflow. I also had a chat with two product teammates, and along with my recent thoughts, I took some time to brainstorm ideas.</p> <p>Lately, I came across another person doing a “Build in Public 100 Days” challenge, also working on a travel app. Several friends mentioned it to me today and even asked if we were on the same team—haha. This also led me to write an article yesterday reflecting on our product, going back to the core idea, and defining why our product can survive in the market, what makes it different, and what value it brings to users. This actually helped me further clarify my thoughts. I believe delivering a good product to the market isn’t the hard part—survival is. Entering the travel planning app space sometimes feels like “seeking my own demise.” After all, the dominant players in this industry are OTAs (Online Travel Agencies), which hold the key B2B resources and have massive user bases—an enormous moat. On the other hand, many products that started as tools have struggled to monetize, leading to shutdowns. Another challenge is the low barrier to entry—many people can build similar products, and independent creators often go for small, niche, and paid products.</p> <p>So, why start despite all this? Anyone with some business knowledge can analyze these challenges, but I believe the world still needs a bit of irrationality and courage. Andrea used a word today that I found fitting—Utopia. Deep down, my rational self still holds a touch of impulsive passion, perhaps influenced by my wild, self-taught experience in the arts. I enjoy painting bold strokes of creativity against a logical backdrop.</p> <p>Right now, no single app allows me to fully manage my travel experience from start to finish. Travelers today are “Frankenstein users,” constantly piecing together information from different sources, recording bits here and there. Travel can be a one-time, fleeting joy or a lifelong collection of experiences—it all depends on how you define it. I want to create an app that I can use for a lifetime.</p> <p>Current Progress:</p> <ul> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 28%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 27%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Development: 8%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ul> <p>If you match the following criteria, let’s talk! (We’re looking for a UI designer 👾)</p> <ol> <li>Commitment</li> <li>Dreams</li> <li>Passion &amp; Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣1️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 30/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-30-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 30/100days"/><published>2025-03-18T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-18T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-30-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-30-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣0️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-18-iter-x-30-100/Wiki.2025-03-18_23-12-12-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-18-iter-x-30-100/Wiki.2025-03-18_23-12-12-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-18-iter-x-30-100/Wiki.2025-03-18_23-12-12-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-18-iter-x-30-100/Wiki.2025-03-18_23-12-12.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Wiki </div> <p>Time flies so quickly—it’s already been 30 days, and we’ve completed 1/3 of the journey. Without realizing it, our small team has grown to 13 people. Today, some team members shared a few competitions, both AI-focused and startup-related. We plan to participate in a few and see how we can contribute. This also pushes us to quickly deliver some demos and prepare investment pitch materials. We expect to have a working demo this week; both the client and AI components are still being worked on. The team is deeply focused on the overall AI framework and ensuring everything flows smoothly. We aim to have everything up and running by tomorrow or the day after at the latest.</p> <p>We should be launching an official account soon to post content, though we haven’t fully decided on the content production strategy yet. That’s it for now—back to work.</p> <p>Current Status Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 27%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 26%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) progress: 8%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (maybe take a look at Day 6 for more context):</p> <ol> <li>Can persist</li> <li>Have a dream</li> <li>Have an interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣0️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 29/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-29-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 29/100days"/><published>2025-03-17T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-17T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-29-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-29-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣9️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-17-iter-x-29-100/DailyItinerary.2025-03-18_00-11-18-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-17-iter-x-29-100/DailyItinerary.2025-03-18_00-11-18-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-17-iter-x-29-100/DailyItinerary.2025-03-18_00-11-18-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-17-iter-x-29-100/DailyItinerary.2025-03-18_00-11-18.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Daily Itinerary </div> <p>Two new teammates have joined the team, filling the gap in product operations. We also have a C-end product role now—looking forward to future outputs!</p> <p>Today, I focused on handling the AI architecture. It’s mostly sorted out, and tomorrow, I’ll integrate an instance to connect the entire process. On the backend side, we plan to integrate MCP and align with some open-source protocols. MCP itself is an initiative aimed at resolving the chaotic Function Call implementations across different vendors. This should have been something OpenAI led, but since it’s focused on for-profit commercialization, Claude has taken up the mantle. MCP was released last year but has only recently gained traction among developers. Now, various services are starting to build MCP Servers for their platforms. Currently, the only usable client-side applications seem to be Cursor and the Claude app, and an MCP application marketplace is expected to emerge rapidly.</p> <p>If you’re a UI designer, feel free to reach out! Right now, I’m also handling UI design. While I can translate my ideas into designs effectively, we still need a designer with a unique style and vision to elevate the overall design.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 27%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 25%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 7%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, let’s chat! (Maybe check out Day 6 first):</p> <ol> <li>Commitment</li> <li>Dreams</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣9️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 28/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-28-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 28/100days"/><published>2025-03-16T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-16T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-28-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-28-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣8️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-16-iter-x-28-100/TripPage.2025-03-16_23-45-09-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-16-iter-x-28-100/TripPage.2025-03-16_23-45-09-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-16-iter-x-28-100/TripPage.2025-03-16_23-45-09-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-16-iter-x-28-100/TripPage.2025-03-16_23-45-09.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Trip Page </div> <p>This weekend, I’ve mainly been working on the design of the AI architecture. The PR is still in DRAFT status and isn’t fully completed yet; it’s expected to take another two days to finish. In the evenings, I managed to spare some time to refactor and optimize the main itinerary page. It’s still a half-finished project, but over the past month of practice, my understanding of prototype + UI design has improved. However, there’s still a long way to go in terms of aesthetics. I plan to take some time to further develop my taste and artistic sense. I actually get quite anxious when I see others’ designs not aligning with my vision. I think many people feel the same way—most will just say they don’t like something or that it’s not good enough, but they might struggle to pinpoint exactly what’s wrong. I’m really fond of the concept of being a polymath or a learned person, someone who has deep knowledge in a few areas. For an independent creator, it feels like knowing just one thing isn’t enough. You need to have unique insights in several areas to see clearly on the big picture and understand the details as well.</p> <p>Cursor, Windsurf, Claude Code, MCP—if you haven’t been paying attention to these keywords lately, you might want to take note. These are currently trending in the frontier fields, and I’ve been experimenting with applying them in real projects and engineering. There are a lot of thoughts and feelings around this. AI replacing most jobs is definitely not just hype. If you try it seriously, you’ll be disheartened to realize how fragile many professions are under the relentless forward momentum of AI. Based on this, you have to stay on track and not get left behind. Don’t be fooled by the overwhelming Demo-style marketing online. Many exaggerated self-media channels can gradually lull you into complacency. The consequence is that you’ll miss out on new trends simply because you weren’t aware. If you want to exchange ideas or learn about the latest trends in AI, feel free to reach out to me. It’s completely free. I hope to create a small group where we can exchange cutting-edge information, follow relevant papers, news, and startup updates. If you’re interested, feel free to follow me and DM me.</p> <p>Summary of current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 26%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 24%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 6%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (or you can first check out Day 6’s content):</p> <ol> <li>Can persist</li> <li>Has dreams</li> <li>Has interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣8️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 27/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-27-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 27/100days"/><published>2025-03-15T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-15T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-27-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-27-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day2️⃣7️⃣</p> <p>Today I’ve been focusing on the overall architecture and framework of the AI. The plan is to first implement the PlanAgent and streamline the process, so that the entire framework is thought through and other people can contribute based on this direction. I’m planning to stick to the previous design where we register multiple agents, and each agent can register a series of toolsets. This way, each agent can share tools when handling specific tasks. Currently, agents don’t communicate with each other, because the main goal right now is to integrate AI into the business layer’s various modules. Later, when we have a fully controlled AI, we will extract a main scheduling role in the business layer, where we can consider implementing multi-agent coordination to complete a task. This will also integrate routing gating. Overall, we’ll still follow a multi-layered architecture where the upper layers can repeatedly reuse lower-layer instances, and lower layers are treated as “atomic capabilities” by the upper layers.</p> <p>Summary of the current situation:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 25%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 23%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 6%</li> <li>Data: 6%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (maybe check out Day 6 first):</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day2️⃣7️⃣]]></summary></entry></feed>