<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-04-04T15:36:56+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ifuryst</title><subtitle>📝 &amp; 💭 </subtitle><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 46/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-46-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 46/100days"/><published>2025-04-03T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-03T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-46-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-46-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣6️⃣</p> <p>I’ve adjusted the AI again. I’m planning to use Function Call’s JSON return to achieve a stable structured JSON output. Essentially, I’m tricking the AI by using a tool that doesn’t actually exist or need execution. Normally, we rely on prompts to request a JSON response, but that approach doesn’t seem to guarantee 100% stability.</p> <p>I’ve also further broken down the agents into more atomic units. Now, each agent handles a very specific task, making it easier to reuse their functions. For example, I’ve separated CityPlanner and TripPlanner, so if the destination city is unknown, AI can first plan the cities before diving into the itinerary. Over the next couple of days, I’ll focus on connecting the entire itinerary module, which will bring the core functionality to life.</p> <p>It’s hard to believe that nearly half of the 100-day journey has passed. The intensity of daily output is quite demanding, especially since some days don’t show obvious progress. The public is mostly visual-oriented, and I don’t want to dig into too many technical details because that would be even more tedious. Instead, I mix in insights and news occasionally. If I build in public again in the future, I might consider sharing in phases rather than posting daily updates. I don’t want the content to become a monotonous log—I’d rather deliver it when there’s something valuable to share.</p> <p>Current Progress: • Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33% • Backend (Go) Development: 36% • Client (Flutter) Development: 25% • Data: 10%</p> <p>If you meet the following criteria, let’s connect:</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Ambitious</li> <li>Passionate</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣6️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 45/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-45-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 45/100days"/><published>2025-04-02T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-02T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-45-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-45-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣5️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MainTripPage2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePageSkeleton-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePageSkeleton-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePageSkeleton-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePageSkeleton.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePage-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePage-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePage-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-02-iter-x-45-100/MinePage.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Main Trip Page &amp; Mine Page </div> <p>Still working on the pages. I plan to integrate the itinerary this week and check if I’m going anywhere for the Qingming Festival. If not, I should be able to finish it. The progress has been good these past two days. I will reassess the overall progress next week. These tasks are being pushed forward based on my intuition, not following a strict timeline, which I think is one of the challenges in project management. If there was a clear roadmap and the requirements were well-defined, progress could be more predictable and manageable. Otherwise, it’s difficult to smoothly advance the project. Right now, we’re still in a chaotic state, and everything is growing wildly, which is a significant issue. However, we could consider introducing a simple visual dashboard to track our MVP progress. But because the collaboration is quite loose, it’s challenging to bring in project management tools commonly used in the industry. This is a bit of a paradox, and I’ll need to think about and learn more about it. The goal is not to add unnecessary complexity, but to make sure everyone on the team clearly understands the current project status—where the bottlenecks are, where they stand, and what others are working on. These insights would be meaningful.</p> <p>Here’s the current summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 34%</li> <li>Frontend (Flutter) progress: 23%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we need a UI designer 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dreamer</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣5️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 44/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-44-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 44/100days"/><published>2025-04-01T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-01T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-44-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-44-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣4️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/cursor-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/cursor-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/cursor-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/cursor.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> POI </div> <p>Today, we made significant progress with our POI data. Our new team member has been incredibly helpful, successfully running the data source and processing many POI records. In three days, after another team member who is currently traveling returns, we’ll review the ETL logic, and we can begin the data cleaning process.</p> <p>I spent the day immersed in n8n workflow orchestration. There are some tasks I can automate using n8n, which will help improve my efficiency and productivity. I think investing time in this is worthwhile. For example, I can quickly push articles I’ve written to different platforms through some custom nodes and workflows. Another thing is information aggregation and dimensionality reduction. I’ve been consuming a lot of information daily, and I need to aggregate it to reduce redundant news. This way, I can allocate more time to reading in-depth articles. Having a broad yet precise strategy allows me to stay on top of the latest trends while also exploring interesting ideas. I’ll share more on this topic later.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/poi-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/poi-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/poi-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-04-01-iter-x-44-100/poi.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Cursor </div> <p>I also saw Anysphere, the startup behind Cursor. They expect to generate $200 million in Annual Recurring Revenue (ARR) through subscriptions over the next 12 months. They’re currently raising a new round of funding, and their valuation is expected to reach $10 billion. This company currently has only 50 employees, which is impressive. Their success is largely due to early popularity within developer circles and winning Product Hunt’s 2024 Product of the Year award. Since then, they’ve continued to gain popularity. Their net revenue retention rate (NRR) for March 2024 reached an astounding 250%. What does this mean? It indicates that their existing customers are not only continuing to pay but are also paying more—$1 per customer is now $2.50. A typical NRR of 115% is already considered excellent, as it signifies steady revenue growth from existing customers. So, Cursor’s NRR is truly remarkable. Personally, I’m not surprised at all. I think Cursor has surpassed traditional IDEs and has become the new standard. JetBrains products seem to have stagnated. Recently, I’ve been using it extensively for creating SOP manuals and training documents for my team to refer to before starting new tasks. The results have been incredible. One of my team members, whom I introduced to it, couldn’t stop praising it and spent the entire day watching AI-related content. I’ll share more on this topic later. If you’re still in the camp of not using it or criticizing it as hard to use, I urge you to reconsider. I believe you’ll soon realize that others are moving ahead, and if you think it’s hard to use, try to see if you’re using it incorrectly or misjudging the AI’s capabilities, leading to incorrect results. Don’t let simple biases stop you from learning and mastering new things.</p> <p>Current Progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX Design: 33%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 34%</li> <li>Frontend (Flutter) Progress: 21%</li> <li>Data: 10%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you fit the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we’re looking for a UI designer 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Persistent</li> <li>Dreamer</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣4️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 43/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-43-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 43/100days"/><published>2025-03-31T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-31T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-43-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-43-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣3️⃣</p> <p>From the overall progress, it seems that we’ve only completed about 1/3 of the total, but I’m still quite confident that we’ll finish the rest in the next 50 days, so the whole process doesn’t seem to be linear. This is understandable; at the beginning, there are a lot of things to handle. After completing a few pages or APIs, many things can be reused, so the speed naturally picks up.</p> <p>Today, I was looking into Bluesky’s ATProtocol. Although I had seen it before, I hadn’t carefully examined its technical architecture. After reading an article analyzing it, I started thinking about whether a decentralized blockchain social platform could become the next big trend. After all, the Web3 buzz has been going on for quite a while. But on second thought, our travel app could also explore this direction. Although it feels a bit like a tech utopia, if the app doesn’t really take off in the future, I would consider fully open-sourcing it and integrating ATProtocol or creating a custom decentralized travel protocol. In this case, the app would simply be an AppView, a display carrier, and the data would be mostly consensus-based on the blockchain. Users would own their own data, which could be a fun and innovative concept.</p> <p>Last night, I recorded a screen capture of the current client situation. After doing a bit of hands-on work, I’m starting to get a feel for it. I look forward to recording another screen capture this week to share. Over the past few days, I’ve been receiving messages from new friends who are sharing or asking about features in the app. I’m happy to continuously receive private messages, and we actively consider many great suggestions. If you have any ideas, feel free to reach out to me for a chat.</p> <p>Summary of current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 32%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 33%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) development: 20%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we are looking for a UI design partner 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Able to persevere</li> <li>Dreamer</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣3️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 42/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-42-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 42/100days"/><published>2025-03-30T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-30T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-42-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-42-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣2️⃣</p> <p>Today, I worked on a page. If I can keep up this speed, it won’t be long before I can finish the remaining pages. Over the next couple of days, I’ll need to supplement the backend interfaces. Since I stopped drawing every day, the progress has really picked up! It’s important to balance things out. For anyone considering independent development, there are a few things we need to handle for an app:</p> <ol> <li>Setting up the code structure and basic framework (this is crucial, but if you have experience with past projects, it’s usually quick).</li> <li>Product brainstorming — those with capability will output mind maps and wireframes.</li> <li>Design work (depending on the size of the product, this can go quickly or slowly, but it’s a significant task).</li> <li>Database design (for more complex products, this is a major job, but I usually produce this along with backend development).</li> <li>Backend development (its importance depends on the product’s target scale).</li> <li>Frontend/client-side development (end users are visual beings, while B2B is more function-driven).</li> <li>Integration and testing, reviewing design implementation (details always take up a lot of time and energy, depending on the scale and whether you’re a perfectionist).</li> </ol> <p>These are the main areas. If you’re not simply building a few pages or a design-focused product, as complexity increases, you’ll need to invest in all of these directions. It’s clear that for independent developers, building a team to handle all these aspects requires a huge amount of effort 🧑🏿‍💻.</p> <p>Summary of current progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 32%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 32%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) progress: 19%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we need a UI design partner 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Can persevere</li> <li>Has dreams</li> <li>Is interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣2️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 41/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-41-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 41/100days"/><published>2025-03-29T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-29T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-41-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-41-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣1️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-29-iter-x-41-100/GitHubContributions-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-29-iter-x-41-100/GitHubContributions-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-29-iter-x-41-100/GitHubContributions-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-29-iter-x-41-100/GitHubContributions.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> GitHub Contributions </div> <p>Today, I was busy coding and really immersed in it. I was mainly working on the client side, and seeing the implementation on the real device was amazing. It felt just like transitioning from prototype to high-fidelity design, and it was very satisfying. There’s a creative sense to it, and as I’ve said before, I really enjoy creating. I think it’s an important driving force that can support you for the long haul. I checked my main repository and saw there have been 179 commits. Since Day 0, February 17th, I’ve been consistently pushing updates to GitHub. The fewest commits in a day was 2, and the most was 38. When you feel like you want to do something, build something, or even start a business, you need to ask yourself: can you keep going like this for months or even years? Why do I keep emphasizing the power of persistence? I don’t like it when people simplify everything with the phrase “choice is more important than effort” and use that to negate the value of hard work. If you look at most successful people, the majority are the result of hard work—there’s no shortcut. Going back to the earlier question: knowing is easy, doing is hard. I hope that the fire inside of you keeps burning, and that you don’t let the dullness of the real world easily put it out.</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype &amp; UI/UX design: 32%</li> <li>Backend (Go) development: 32%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) progress: 18%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we need a UI design teammate 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Can persist</li> <li>Have dreams</li> <li>Have an interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣1️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 40/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-40-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 40/100days"/><published>2025-03-28T15:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-28T15:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-40-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-40-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day4️⃣0️⃣</p> <p>At the invitation of KejiShu, I had an online chat with their operations team for nearly an hour today. We mainly conducted an interview focused on independent developers, shared some thoughts on the creative process, and discussed how there is now a wider variety of content on Xiaohongshu (XHS). They are also considering some future features. We even talked about the 18-image + 1K-word limit, which I think is a format that creators in certain fields inevitably encounter. However, this is closely tied to XHS’s product positioning, making it difficult to change.</p> <p>Overall, it was an enjoyable conversation. I love exchanging ideas with different people—many times, these interactions spark new and interesting thoughts. I look forward to seeing them provide more support for independent developers in the future and hope they maintain the platform’s overall community atmosphere and tone. After all, this could be one of the key motivations for many people to continue creating.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/MinePage1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/MinePage1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/MinePage1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/MinePage1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/MinePage2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/MinePage2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/MinePage2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/MinePage2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Mine Page </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/RawMinePage-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/RawMinePage-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/RawMinePage-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/RawMinePage.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/Cursor+Figma1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/Cursor+Figma1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/Cursor+Figma1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/Cursor+Figma1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/Cursor+Figma2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/Cursor+Figma2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/Cursor+Figma2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-28-iter-x-40-100/Cursor+Figma2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Cursor + Figma to codes </div> <p>Over the past two days, I explored two AI-powered efficiency improvements. The day before yesterday, I used Cursor with Figma to generate prototype images from text. Today, I experimented with using Cursor + Figma to convert design files into Flutter client code. I found the results and efficiency gains of the latter more significant.</p> <p>I’ve attached some images—by using the simplest prompts and just two iterations, I generated a 60%-complete page. After spending some time refining it, I got the final version. I think this approach is something I’ll continue experimenting with, as I aim to maximize my efficiency.</p> <p>Today, someone with their own product ideas joined our team and will help us focus on data preparation for POI recommendations. I’m happy to see talented people continuing to join us. Our two product teammates are also actively discussing ideas and defining features.</p> <p>One interesting aspect is that while our prototypes, design files, and development have all progressed to a certain extent, the complete product definition is still catching up. This is mainly because the product team joined later. Initially, I was the one conceptualizing everything, so now we’re running on two parallel tracks. However, I remain optimistic—most functional elements shouldn’t deviate too much, and UI/UX refinements can be adjusted quickly with some additional effort but still within a manageable scope.</p> <p>Current Progress Summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX Design: 32%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 32%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Development: 17%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, we’d love to chat! (We’re looking for a UI Designer 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Persistence</li> <li>Ambition</li> <li>Passion</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day4️⃣0️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 39/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-39-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 39/100days"/><published>2025-03-27T15:50:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-27T15:50:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-39-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-39-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣9️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-27-iter-x-39-100/MinePage-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-27-iter-x-39-100/MinePage-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-27-iter-x-39-100/MinePage-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-27-iter-x-39-100/MinePage.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Mine Page </div> <p>There isn’t any major progress update today, but our new UI teammate has started helping with some optimizations. Everyone is making progress in their respective areas, and we’ll push hard again this weekend. I also worked on the personal profile page a bit—this isn’t the final version yet, just putting in some content for now, and we’ll adjust the layout later.</p> <p>Today, I watched Lei Jun’s 2024 annual speech, and it resonated with me quite a bit. Overall, I have a lot of respect for him. While he’s undoubtedly a marketing genius, I still found some really genuine moments in his talk—especially his approach to making cars. To truly understand the industry, he test-drove over 170 cars, borrowing them from friends, taking 4S store test drives, and even asking strangers in parking lots. He also led his team to obtain racing licenses, experiencing racing firsthand. Betting everything on one final startup, constantly learning and expanding his knowledge—this level of dedication is something I deeply respect. It’s about truly loving what you do.</p> <p>He also mentioned a 21-day closed-door “argument session” with his core team, where they debated until they fully understood the direction before executing.</p> <p>This is perhaps the mindset every entrepreneur should have—stripping away the unnecessary fluff and just focusing on getting things done. There’s no need for grand, empty slogans or overly complex processes. What matters is full commitment from everyone involved. Larger companies often suffer from bureaucracy, pushing employees to become hyper-specialized in their roles. But in a fast-moving team, we need people to be more versatile, aligning under a shared vision to build momentum.</p> <p>Having a deep understanding of what you’re working on is crucial. Just like with our product—we need to first develop our own perspectives on travel before we can shape the product around those insights. Only then can we define our individual roles within this project.</p> <p>I also came across some great quotes about travel while reading a magazine today, but I forgot to take pictures. I’ll jot them down tomorrow and share them!</p> <p>Current Progress:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 31%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 31%</li> <li>Client (Flutter) Progress: 14%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>We’re Looking for a UI Designer 👾!</p> <p>If you match the following, let’s talk:</p> <ol> <li>Commitment</li> <li>Dreams</li> <li>Passion &amp; Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣9️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 38/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-38-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 38/100days"/><published>2025-03-26T14:30:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-26T14:30:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-38-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-38-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣8️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3"> <div class="row mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="row mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="row mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design3-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/cursor+figma.design3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/deepseek.design-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/deepseek.design-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/deepseek.design-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-26-iter-x-38-100/deepseek.design" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> Cursor &amp; Figma Design(left), DeepSeek Design(right) </div> <p>Today I explored generating prototype images with AI: deepseek for HTML, and cursor + Figma for Figma designs. It provided some useful ideas, and prototyping exploration was helpful. However, the prompts still need some tuning. I’ll share a few of the results.</p> <p>I’ll continue exploring this area, with the ideal process being:</p> <ol> <li>Cursor + Figma to generate prototype or design images.</li> <li>Designers intervene to optimize and finalize the design.</li> <li>Then use Figma + Cursor to quickly generate code.</li> <li>Manual inspection and adjustments.</li> </ol> <p>This approach can help improve efficiency and is suitable for long-term, sustainable progress. It’s like that well-worn saying, “AI won’t replace you, but those who know how to use AI will replace you.” In the internet era, we used to say it’s no longer the time for big fish to eat small fish, but for fast fish to eat slow fish. I think this phrase is even more fitting for the AI era. The speed of AI advancements is beyond my imagination. I thought of the word “momentum,” which originally refers to kinetic energy in physics, but in news or articles, it’s often used to describe a project, team, or event’s development momentum. I think it’s a good fit for the AI era. While AI agents and MCPs are already last year’s things (I’ve thought about this: new technology takes time to flow from research to market, commercial, or public view. Many things last year were still in papers, and we’re part of the early adopters, so it feels a bit surreal and even confusing, but then it hits us—we realize the speed is just overwhelming), the applications emerging this year are coming faster and in greater numbers. If you can’t keep up, you won’t stay in place, but rather fall behind on the conveyor belt of time. The reason I work hard to absorb a lot of information, think, learn, and practice is to counter the rigidity that comes with age and experience.</p> <p>As for the team, today two new members joined, focusing on data and UI design. We’re now 15 people. Do you think that’s too many? Have you seen this kind of collaboration style? After the MVP launch, if I have time, I’ll write about the story behind this product.</p> <p>Here’s the current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX Design: 30%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 31%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 14%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you think you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we need a UI design partner 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Persistence</li> <li>Dream-driven</li> <li>Interest</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣8️⃣]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[Iter-X] 37/100days</title><link href="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-37-100/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Iter-X] 37/100days"/><published>2025-03-25T14:59:59+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-25T14:59:59+00:00</updated><id>https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-37-100</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ifuryst.github.io/blog/2025/iter-x-37-100/"><![CDATA[<p>Day3️⃣7️⃣</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/2-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/3-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/4-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/4-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/4-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/4.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/5-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/5-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/5-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/5.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/6-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/6-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/6-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/6.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/7-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/7-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/7-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/7.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm mt-0 mb-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/8-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/8-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/8-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/2025-03-25-iter-x-37-100/8.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> </div> <div class="caption mt-0"> App Design Concept </div> <p>Today I continued refining the client-side, almost finished filling in the gaps. Tomorrow, I’ll start pushing pages. I was thinking maybe I should find some time over the next couple of days to also work on the personal page, which should be quick to finalize. Once that’s done, I can focus more on the modules and pages centered around the itinerary.</p> <p>Reve.art gained some popularity today, and I tried it out—it’s still very effective! The free credits are being replenished quickly, and it’s great for exploring ideas. AI-generated images are really useful for inspiration, but finding the right direction still requires personal input. There are still some issues with style consistency, for example, generating multiple scenes based on one character often yields unreliable results. However, images and videos are certainly hot areas right now. I think many businesses could benefit from this, especially with platforms like Jianying, which deeply integrates this functionality, really increasing willingness to pay.</p> <p>Current progress summary:</p> <ol> <li>Prototype Design &amp; UI/UX: 30%</li> <li>Backend (Go) Development: 31%</li> <li>Client-side (Flutter) Progress: 13%</li> <li>Data: 8%</li> </ol> <p>If you meet the following criteria, feel free to reach out (we’re looking for a UI design teammate 👾):</p> <ol> <li>Perseverance</li> <li>Dreamer</li> <li>Interested</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="products"/><category term="products"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day3️⃣7️⃣]]></summary></entry></feed>